<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100301151556AAOLpQ1" type="Answered">
    <Subject>who knows what I am doing in the Internet?</Subject>
    <Content>I heard that isc have the ability to watch whatever I am doing on the internet, but I only uses wireless adaptor the steal signal from other, would anyone knows what exactly I am doing?
it was something about the IP address or something, I want to hide it if there&#039;s anyway. thanks
lol, I am not watching porns! I am thinking about cyber crime
I heard about ghost surf where you go online without your ip being seen?
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-01 15:15:56</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267485356</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100301151556AAOLpQ1</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>LB5OP0kDaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Tommy</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>5</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>It is &quot;technically&quot; illegal to pirate off someone else&#039;s wireless signal, however, since they left it unsecured, they are &quot;technically&quot; responsible for how it&#039;s used.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>eCvX6Nceaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Twist</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267485743</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268251981</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>you were watching porn...</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>6AtCYne8aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>=D</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 15:17:28</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267485448</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Your ISP( internet service provider) can see what your doing, if they cared to, which is unlikely. but if your stealing the signal from elsewhere they would get the rap initially, until they checked the ip adress assigned tot heir computer and realized it didnt match. anyone with a little technical knowhow on your computer could tell, but really, your completely fine.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>yjnTXjFqaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Jesse G</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 15:19:20</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267485560</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>It is not illegal to go on someones internet if they dont have it password protected i think. But they could only see what you were doing if they are smart and can view the router logs but i doubt they do this so you should be fine and they wont know your even on their connection</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>WSnK722Uaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Liam</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 15:20:20</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267485620</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>It is &quot;technically&quot; illegal to pirate off someone else&#039;s wireless signal, however, since they left it unsecured, they are &quot;technically&quot; responsible for how it&#039;s used.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>eCvX6Nceaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Twist</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 15:22:23</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267485743</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>anyone who realy wants too can fugure out what u are doing online
google keeps a record of everything u search, as dous yahoo and the others, and u cant hide your ip address. If you are logged into any emaExample if u type in wether into google it will give u weather for a place neer u becouse your ip gives away your location, also when a site knows you, like on ask when u set a theme, next time u go on the theme is still there becouse ask knows u are on the same computer</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>veUaQkyVaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>akaanwers</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 15:23:31</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267485811</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws11.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:30:10 PDT 2010 -->
