<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100322064719AAP5BTU" type="Answered">
    <Subject>E-Bay listing question ?</Subject>
    <Content>Ok so this may take a while...

What i have is different sized coloured pumps but the thing is i want to list them on e-bay but i don&#039;t want to create a new listing every time i do each one of them and what i seen on some listings on e bay is there were shoes and when you buy them there was an Option to choose what size you want colour etc. does anyone know how to do this option when creating a listing for shoes. Taaank you so much guys :***
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-22 06:47:19</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269265639</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100322064719AAP5BTU</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>3LxBN1t4aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Mee</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1h0UM1lcxAAED4eQzLb4qCw==.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>own load the turbo lister tool</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>AA10871086</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>bigian1179</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269265929</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269785019</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>own load the turbo lister tool</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>AA10871086</UserId>
            <UserNick>bigian1179</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-22 06:52:09</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269265929</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Not sure about the Turbo listing being much help but it might be?  If you have say 10 of size 5 (UK size) pumps for example you can put one auction on them all in one go and people buy however many they want. You pay Ebay one listing fee for the auction but a final value fee for each pair sold.  Costs you much less than listing each pair individually. 

Then once they are successfully listed you use the &quot;sell similar&quot; button for your next auction just change the pump size to 6 (UK 39) for example and the number for sale to 15 or however many pairs you have. Using the &quot;sell similar&quot; saves a lot of hassle as all the information stays the same unless you change something and you can use the same photo (as long as they all look the same) and the P&amp;P will be the same each time.  

Don&#039;t forget to offer a postage discount if people buy more than one pair. Work it out and enter it so they don&#039;t have to message you to ask.</Content>
            <Reference>Ebay member since 2002</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>6JYnwZCwaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Trust Me I&#039;m a Doctor ♥</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-25 13:26:32</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269548792</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws15.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:23:50 PDT 2010 -->
