<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100302183647AAAednU" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Why is my internet connection very slow periodically?</Subject>
    <Content>Recently for the past month, I&#039;ve been getting weird internet connections. Everything will be fine for a few hours, then it would slow down, and appear to have over a second of latency for everything (eg. Firefox, IE, downloads, gaming). And about 40mins~1 hour or so after, it goes back to normal, then the cycle repeats. This happens to both of my wired and wireless connections.

When this happens, restarting my router or modem brings the speed back up, but it doesn&#039;t seem like there&#039;s anything wrong on my end since the latency goes away after a period of time. I&#039;ve also not found any viruses that could potentially use up all my bandwidth.

I tried calling my internet provider, and they have failed to find the root of the problem. Their suggestions were 1) Restarting the router/modem, 2) Someone might be using my internet, and 3) A virus might be causing this. But since this happens so often, simply restarting my router or modem everytime it happens is not an efficient solution. I have also double checked, my internet is secure with a difficult password, and nobody seems to be using judging it from the list of active+inactive MAC addresses.

Could someone please help me out? Thanks!
Edit:

Like I said, it doesn&#039;t seem to be a problem with my router or modem, since the latency goes away and my internet connections go back to normal after a while even without having to restart the router+modem. &gt;&lt;
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-02 18:36:47</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267583807</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100302183647AAAednU</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>mbB1DK3Taa</UserId>
    <UserNick>SNaiLs</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/10Tj-r0o-AAICTcNwPJNuAluiy0UMlhgU3TZk.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Have check you pc make sure why is your pc is slow.
 http://registry.tp5pro.com/Slow_PC</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>lZIaR8o3aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>JamesCameronsAvatar</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267895904</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268103269</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Get either a new modem or wifi adapter</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>i4MOCxgeaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Dan</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-02 18:48:47</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267584527</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Have check you pc make sure why is your pc is slow.
 http://registry.tp5pro.com/Slow_PC</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>lZIaR8o3aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>JamesCameronsAvatar</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 09:18:24</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267895904</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws06.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:23:04 PDT 2010 -->
