<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100326040923AAnJW3U" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Is there a service that allows you to track if a link was clicked and by who?</Subject>
    <Content>Please Read Carefully before you answer to make sure you understand what I am asking.

First, I do NOT want to know how to track my own personal affiliate links that I promote.

I have a successful website and have recently decided to start an affiliate program.  When I send out the affiliate newsletter I will be including some links for some specific purposes.  I want to know if there is a service or tracker that will track  1 - If a link was clicked and 2 If it was clicked, which affiliates clicked on it. And then giving me a report that shows me how many clicks the link got and a list of the affiliates who clicked on it.

I appreciate all honest and informative answers.  


WARNING: If you are one of those answers that click on a bunch of questions and leave BS answers just to get credit for answering a question, please know that I will give the answer a thumbs down and report you to yahoo and then you will be blocked.  I dont do this to have to wade through a bunch of uninformative, bs answers.  Its a waste of my time and I will take action.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-26 04:09:23</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269601763</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100326040923AAnJW3U</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>jQQbpquVaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>BernBabyBern</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/4b023827i1defzul7re4/.4aTQ049caQ1t6OrEb0AbOHJSA--/1/tn48.jpg?ciAAToMBMo.uTQrs</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Sure sounds like you would want to use a complete affiliate management package, apparently one CPA management service (I forgot the name) costs thousands a month (I hear DirectTrack costs $10k to setup).
  I&#039;ve heard of some big affiliate marketers who recruit clients away from affiliate networks use this software with themselves as the sole affiliate to serve their private clients.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>pUsyQePmaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Jakester</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269636722</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269919747</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>to your warning :O and b4 u report me....

Im not sure if you can track if it was clicked or not but you can track how many people visited a page, so if the link goes to a specific web page you can track how many people visited that page, and u can see from where that page was viewed (machine picks it up by IP address) it wont tell you the exact location but it will give you a general area ie. Melbourne, Aus</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>mjv9b3R1aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Roan</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-26 04:16:44</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269602204</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Sure sounds like you would want to use a complete affiliate management package, apparently one CPA management service (I forgot the name) costs thousands a month (I hear DirectTrack costs $10k to setup).
  I&#039;ve heard of some big affiliate marketers who recruit clients away from affiliate networks use this software with themselves as the sole affiliate to serve their private clients.</Content>
            <Reference>*** Affiliate management scripts
Freebies
http://www.hotscripts.com/category/php/scripts-programs/affiliate-programs/
17 inhouse affiliate package mini reviews
http://www.cumbrowski.com/Inhouseprogram.asp
Adapp-HasOffers service: free/$99/$799
http://hasoffers.com/
http://jam.jrox.com/ JAM $250
iDevAffiliate.com  $99 - $299
http://forums.digitalpoint.com/showthread.php?t=1645961</Reference>
            <Best>4</Best>
            <UserId>pUsyQePmaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Jakester</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-26 13:52:02</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269636722</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I know a website that would track only the number of links on your website but not track by who clicked them. Tracking your affiliate URL is really useful especially if you&#039;re promoting your website thru advertising. I know a website which do not only track your affiliate link but protect them as well. It&#039;s on the link below. Just check if it&#039;s what you need.

http://com-vipdetails.info</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>9HYKW5BGaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>BestHomeProfits.com</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-29 08:17:19</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269875839</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws03.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:27:51 PDT 2010 -->
