<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100316232513AA2yArw" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Youtube video to mp3 converter?</Subject>
    <Content>I recently got the BLACK SCREEN OF DEATH (KSOD), so i lost my bookmarks (I was able to recover my pictures, music, etc). I had one bookmark to a website that converted youtube videos to mp3. 

It allowed you to set the start/end time you wanted to download, and also the information of the file (title, artist, album...)! I think it let you download them as mp4&#039;s too.. 

Please, does anyone know what website this was? I remember the website background was black... if that helps.

Even if it isn&#039;t that exact website, can someone find one that does all of that?

Thank you so much, in advance!
I&#039;m looking for a website, not a program
(I think it&#039;s faster/easier to do it that way)

But I already have TVC (thanks, anyway)
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-16 23:25:13</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268807113</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100316232513AA2yArw</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>sQ6l5uTRaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>carthy</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>15</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I knew  ddvideo video to audio converter gain,I feel well</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>lhrz8DOraa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Johnson</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268837308</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269244932</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Total Video converter 

this is best software not only convert to mp3. u can convert to anything 3gp, avi, mpeg, flash .and so on....... try this it surely help u</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>VUZqbAmsaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Sathish</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-16 23:33:36</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268807616</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>hey you can download a nice software which is &quot;Format Factory&quot; it is free of cost, just download and install it in your computer and you can convert your all you-tube downloaded videos into any sound format like mp3,wav,ogg,mp4,aac etc... You can download it from here:-
http://formatoz.com</Content>
            <Reference>http://formatoz.com</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>14G9urRqaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>abhi thakur</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-16 23:33:52</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268807632</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I recommend a professional youtube video converter.It is Nidesoft Youtube Video Converter.It helps you to download YouTube video from YouTube and convert YouTube video to many other formats: MP4, AVI, MPEG, MP3, WMV,etc.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>McODRkjYaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Misgreen</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-16 23:40:52</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268808052</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Try Leawo Video Converter which can convert videos and audios with video editing fucntions. leawo video converter is an all in one video converter which can
1, Convert videos and audios between popular formats: AVI, MOV, MP4, MPEG, WMV, MOV, DivX, Xvid, VOB, ASF, MPG, MP3, WMA, 3GP, RM, RMVB, DV, TS, etc. 
2, Burn videos to DVD with DVD menu. First, use Leawo to convet video to VOB, then use free star burn ( www.flash-video-mx.com/starburn/ ) to burn the VOB file to DVD. 
3, Crop, trim and merge video files. you can download Leawo video converter here------------------------
For windows:   http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;q=leawo+video+converter&amp;aq=f&amp;aqi=&amp;oq=
For mac:     http://search.yahoo.com/search;_ylt=A0oGkirrVZxLU1UAsaJXNyoA?p=site%3Aleawo.com+mac+video+converter&amp;fr2=sb-top&amp;fr=yfp-t-701&amp;fp_ip=cn&amp;rd=r1&amp;meta=vc%3Dcn&amp;sao=0</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>yz717BqYaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Bamid</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-16 23:43:09</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268808189</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Im using SnowFox Video Converter, i think it could meet all the requirements above, but the website background is gray not black. u can check it.
http://www.snowfoxsoft.com/video-converter.html
Good luck.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>I2NPo2cXaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>CoCo W</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 00:10:45</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268809845</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I recommend you a useful and free tool that can convert video, rip dvd, Backup DVD and download YouTube video. 

it called &quot;Next Video Converter&quot;. It is easy to use, you only need click few button.
Next Video Converter is a free video converter and DVD ripper with easy-to-use graphical interface, fast converting speed, and excellent video quality. It can convert almost all video formats including DivX, XviD, MOV, RM, RMVB, MPEG, VOB, DVD, WMV, and AVI to MPEG-4 movie format for iPod, iPhone, PSP or other portable video device, MP4 player, or Smartphones. It can also rip DVD to any video format.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>CniDjRkGaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Ferga</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 00:28:05</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268810885</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Here&#039;s a link to a nice converter.

http://www.sendspace.com/file/4fdbhc

Enjoy.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>mBqv2Ztzaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Yesterday</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 00:59:27</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268812767</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>There is a free software can help you.at first you should download youtube videos to your computer harddrive, more websites can download youtube videos, like keepvid.com, etc. then you can use RZ MP3 Converter, it is freeware, and can convert any videos or audios to mp3 audios, such as convert youtube videos to mp3. you can yahoo or google search and download RZ MP3 Converter, good quality, easy to use, hope it can help you.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>5vvje4tWaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Mond</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 01:09:16</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268813356</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>If you cannot find a useful converter, I recommend you Altysoft Video converter

It supports so many devices and video formats, such as: iPod, iPhone, PSP, Zune, Xbox, Nokia, avi, wmv, 3gp, mov, flv and more into avi, mov, asf, wmv, mp4, 3gp and others.

Altysoft Video Converter is a very easy and powerful DVD ripping software, which can convert DVD to various formats.

Altysoft Video Converter can help copy whole DVD to your hard diver, then you can burn them to blank DVD using burning software. 

Beside above-mentioned functions, it so easy to download YouTube videos from YouTube website, just specify the URL for the video you want to download.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>FmqGFWNraa</UserId>
            <UserNick>David G</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 01:15:49</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268813749</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Yes, of course it is possible. here is the good Youtube Converter, this YouTube Video Converter is designed for YouTube fanatics to convert any video formats MPG, MPEG, MP4, AVI, MOD, etc to YouTube FLV and SWF format. Then you can easily upload to all the video sites like YouTube, Myspace, Yahoo! Video, Google Video, etc.
You can go here to get more information.

http://www.4videosoft.com/youtube-video-converter.html

here is the instruction:
Step 1: Install and run this powerful youtube video Converter.
Step 2:click the “Add File” button to load your video.
Step 3: Select video formats from &quot;Profile&quot; drop-download list
Step 4: Set the special settings such as &quot;trim&quot;,&quot;effect&quot;,etc to cater to your need and click &quot;START&quot; to start your conversion.

Just now go to have a try, hope it is helpful to you.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>0VxG8NQLaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Ryan</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 03:24:20</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268821460</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I knew  ddvideo video to audio converter gain,I feel well</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>lhrz8DOraa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Johnson</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 07:48:28</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268837308</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>can you see the history,Mac video converter is one of the most stable and comprehensive multi format video converters available and is very easy to use. 
http://www.bestvideoconverter.org/
http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;newwindow=1&amp;q=site%3Ahttp%3A%2F%2Fwww.bestvideoconverter.org%2Fvideo+converter&amp;btnG=Search&amp;aq=f&amp;aqi=&amp;aql=&amp;oq=</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>d5wSiX1Baa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Very</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 19:03:17</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268877797</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>this is a great converter so simple it converts any video link below ......... all around video convert! i use always http://www.any-video-converter.com/download-avc-free.php


                    TRUST ME I USE THIS ITS GREAT AMAZING! ALL AROUND WORKING TOO!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>9NZ1Ly6haa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Omid Me 4 speed!</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 19:46:18</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268880378</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I hope the two website can helps u.http://www.ifunia.com/video-converter-mac.html    http://www.ifunia.com/youtube-converter-mac.html</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>PoOokxL2aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Mimi</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 20:18:13</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268882293</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>hi, i use video download studio as a converter. You can have a try. It can convert many formats, such as, FLV, WMV, WMA, AVI, MPG, MPEG, RMVB, RM, RA, MOV, QT, MP4, M4V, DV, DAT, MP3, AAC, etc.  Hope you will like it. http://www.downloadvideos-convert.com/</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>4ILbsvnraa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Norma</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 22:50:51</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268891451</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws08.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:45:58 PDT 2010 -->
