<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100301231330AAAG2L6" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Free Laptop? Can it be done, please read question?</Subject>
    <Content>we all know the spam emails we get, but is it ever not a scam? I&#039;m aware its never free, id like to find an offer that will guarantee said item or equally valued will be sent on completed participation. I&#039;ve heard tell tale that people have gotten one with little hassle, but ya never know when this is legit or just fraud trying to hype that its real and possible. I&#039;d like up to date info, the internet changes quicker than the times, and maybe some legit sites you&#039;ve done this with if anyone has. Fewer offers to do the better also variety in offers. So is this real? if its scam tell me why, I&#039;ve heard it all before and I&#039;ve been doing research, if you say its a scam i hope you can at least tell me what site it was you used(or a friend or family). not just going by what you&#039;ve heard(iv heard it all) I&#039;m hoping something somewhere may be legit. I always read ToS and never use SSN if asked we all know that. And I want a good deal! I cant afford $100 worth of fees even if the items worth $1000. So gimme some good info, something I haven&#039;t heard. Thanks in advance for any info. Also maybe you know of a good site with like minded people probing these sites n telling if they&#039;re legit or scam. I know WOT n BBB but these dont always help..
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-01 23:13:30</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267514010</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100301231330AAAG2L6</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>8fTz4LIQaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>red baphomet</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>A lot of them, yes. But some of them are legit, the ones that have you fill out their sponsers offers. it was on the news one time but I forgot which ones were legit.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>7uLbck8raa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Matt H.</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267519734</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268033621</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>It&#039;s always a scam.

With the amount of work you do to try to get this &quot;free&quot; object, you could easily have earned it at an actual job.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>nsiN6E3zaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Misc Tech Advice</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 23:19:18</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267514358</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>A lot of them, yes. But some of them are legit, the ones that have you fill out their sponsers offers. it was on the news one time but I forgot which ones were legit.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>7uLbck8raa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Matt H.</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-02 00:48:54</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267519734</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws13.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:28:09 PDT 2010 -->
