<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100316074246AAdTrDL" type="Answered">
    <Subject>who do you host with in the UK and who is the best host for my small website idea?</Subject>
    <Content>
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-16 07:42:46</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268750566</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100316074246AAdTrDL</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>9e681f234975bb704fb6578e221bd24caa</UserId>
    <UserNick>David M</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>5</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I host my sites with FutureServers (futureservers.net), I&#039;ve had no problems over the past 5 years and have more than one site hosted with them.

If you asked people with different hosts I&#039;m sure they&#039;d recommend the company they&#039;re with (if the support and services have been good), so really it&#039;s down to personal preference along with what services you require and how much you&#039;re willing to spend.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>D0vcZFhnaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>sharrikanocha</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268751214</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269270210</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I host my sites with FutureServers (futureservers.net), I&#039;ve had no problems over the past 5 years and have more than one site hosted with them.

If you asked people with different hosts I&#039;m sure they&#039;d recommend the company they&#039;re with (if the support and services have been good), so really it&#039;s down to personal preference along with what services you require and how much you&#039;re willing to spend.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>D0vcZFhnaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>sharrikanocha</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-16 07:53:34</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268751214</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>There are some good web hosting comparison sites around, we generally use http://www.hosting-picks.com/ before advising our clients on new hosting - they also have free SEO resources - good for kick starting your new website. From a quick look, Just Host currently seems to be the cheapest and from personal experience, they offer great service.</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.hosting-picks.com/</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>H1D5TzNwaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>ryan</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-16 07:57:20</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268751440</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I suggest you this website http://www.tenhostingreviews.com where you can find a list of the Top 10 Web hosting companies with the best features, support and pricing. You can get everything you need and it&#039;s very easy. Hope this could help you.</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.tenhostingreviews.com</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>MBt1SJq8aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Webmaster</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-16 14:12:19</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268773939</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Take into consideration that web hosting is a global service. It does not matter what country you are located in; US, UK, Canada, Australia or India. It is good to note that the cost of hosting services in most countries is generally a little more expensive in comparison to the same services in Canada and the United States. Specifically, American web hosts offer a much better value for money than any local hosting.

As an experienced webmaster I recommend BH web hosting which I’m sure it would work for you and fulfill all your requirements. They have a really great offer for hosting &amp; I have used them for over 3 yrs now, and have never had a single problem with them.

You can reach reviews about this web hosting provider and its latest DISCOUNT COUPONS at:

http://www.threehosts.com/business/1st

Only $3.95 /month (with discount coupon).

******IMPORTANT********
* This service was awarded the “Best Business Web Hosting OF The Year”.
* If you sign up for this service you will have $75 credits to advertise your website with the google &amp; yahoo search engines for free!
* You Can Register A Free Domain or Use Your Existing Domains. They Support All Domain Names.
****************************

Hope this helps.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>YsXKcAgbaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>David M</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 15:14:03</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268864043</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Take a look at http://www.webhost.uk.net

They offer cheap web hosting plans scaled for all types of websites - small, medium or big.

Support is good and servers are pretty fast as compared to other web hosting companies.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>3rIdpjImaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>WebRocker</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-18 03:23:36</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268907816</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws14.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:50:01 PDT 2010 -->
