<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100223050343AAkzXVD" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Why does my Firefox Web browser suddenly crash down when a game is almost done to load?</Subject>
    <Content>I tried to play games at miniclip.com and when I the game was almost finish loading, the browser suddenly crashed down. I am currently using firefox 3.6. Is it my browser the main problem? Help. Thank you.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-23 05:03:43</Date>
    <Timestamp>1266930223</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100223050343AAkzXVD</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>Xdz5I3wWaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>hanxtix</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>4</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>, problem is for your PC, but if that work, re instal your Browser !!!.........</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>zVu19UBCaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Topi jerami</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267264974</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267449829</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I had a problem `with firefox crashing until I uninstalled a couple of add-ons. I uninstalled firefox then reinstalled and started from scratch</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>kv81hfyPaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>flying scot</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-23 05:11:04</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266930664</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Try it again with IE and if same thing hapen, problem is for your PC, but if that work, re instal your Browser !!!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>jOGwWgigaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Star</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-23 05:12:11</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266930731</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>A computer&#039;s registry is one big database that has numerous files, options, and settings. These settings and options keep changing with every second of you using your PC and can lead to the damage of some of these settings. This causes errors to show up and the computer to crash.  Registry cleaners http://make-a-computer-run-better.com      software scan the computer&#039;s errors and matches all files and settings with the applications that use them. If it identifies any file or setting to be damaged, missing, or corrupted, it provides you with an updated list of the same and also repairs these errors.  Therefore, if your computer keeps crashing and need to fix blue screen of death a good registry cleaner is all you need. Your computer can also cause problems because of redundant files in its registry. Reg cleaners identify all these redundant and junk files that were left over during the uninstalling process of hardware of software and delete them. This makes sure that the &quot;computer keeps crashing&quot; issue is taken care of.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>U3hCgYW7aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Asgsdg</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-23 15:15:11</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266966911</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>, problem is for your PC, but if that work, re instal your Browser !!!.........</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>zVu19UBCaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Topi jerami</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-27 02:02:54</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267264974</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws15.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 02:22:50 PDT 2010 -->
