<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100222112932AAwFTb9" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Can you use a mac code to transfer an existing account?</Subject>
    <Content>I have had to move back home. I am still in contract with talktalk but my mother is out of contract with orange. I wanted to cancel Orange and was told by Talktalk to get a mac code. When I finally got the mac code I was told by talktalk that they are unable to use this as I am an existing customer and they can only use a mac code for a new package. Other people, including orange have said that they should be able to use the code. I was then told by talktalk to ask orange to remove the tag from the line, however they are unwilling to do this until my notice period ends 11th March, when they will say it will take 10 working days and cost £25 to do. I am really confused and worried as different people are telling me different things Is it possible to transfer using a mac code with an existing account? and what can I do to make sure this is done. If not, What is best to do to avoid charges and a long time without internet connection. I am unemployed and need the internet to find a job and accommodation. Thank you for all your help.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-22 11:29:32</Date>
    <Timestamp>1266866972</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100222112932AAwFTb9</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>7CfcJPTyaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Timothy C</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>You &#039;line&#039; is locked to Orange until you get TalkTalk to accept the Mac code.

They won&#039;t do that until Orange has &#039;released&#039; you from your contract .. and Orange expects you to pay for the service until the end of the month .. after which you should be OK to transfer ... 

So I suggest you get the £25 offer in writing &amp; pay it ... otherwise you can carry on arguing with Orange whilst they carry on charging you for another month ...</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>86e0fcff22774bed26d5e5f6773ca754aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Steve B</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1266945519</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267386472</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>You &#039;line&#039; is locked to Orange until you get TalkTalk to accept the Mac code.

They won&#039;t do that until Orange has &#039;released&#039; you from your contract .. and Orange expects you to pay for the service until the end of the month .. after which you should be OK to transfer ... 

So I suggest you get the £25 offer in writing &amp; pay it ... otherwise you can carry on arguing with Orange whilst they carry on charging you for another month ...</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>86e0fcff22774bed26d5e5f6773ca754aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Steve B</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-23 09:18:39</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266945519</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws09.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 02:27:38 PDT 2010 -->
