<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100312110317AAddXj4" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Should twitter replace blogs completely?</Subject>
    <Content>shud blogs be banned? they r 2 long. we ain&#039;t got no time 4 readin em. twitter is kool.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-12 11:03:17</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268420597</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100312110317AAddXj4</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>AA10295366</UserId>
    <UserNick>carrie</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1H-h3tse4AAEB9AFD7F8=.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>What&#039;s the matter with the modern American attention span?! Geez!!</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>cAoBid7oaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>John</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268420949</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268899927</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>What&#039;s the matter with the modern American attention span?! Geez!!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>cAoBid7oaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>John</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 11:09:09</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268420949</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I would tweet: Carrie is rather foolish to state an impromptu solution to the never ending teenage woes in her community.

On my blog I would write how Carrie was earlier when she was a child and when she used to listen to others problems and provide suitable answers rather than jumping to solutions. I would also write how Carrie used to help school children in their home works and how she used to baby sit to children in need. I would describe all this in a blog and also specify what made Carrie to change her persona. 

All this can be done in a blog, but Twitter does not allow me to write in detail and people reading about Carrie would jump to a conclusion based on my single tweet which I mentioned earlier. Which would you prefer? Developing a person&#039;s character or destroying without even blinking an eye by tweeting a 140 character line?

Blogs and Twitter have their own places. None can replace one another. You just need to associate one to another. Tweet in small message and brief it on blog.

Hope you understood.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>xv3sR2Heaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Leenus</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 11:45:12</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268423112</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws09.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:09:18 PDT 2010 -->
