<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100327203347AAJ3m9Z" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Does it hurt your job chances if you never use Web 2.0?</Subject>
    <Content>I have a degree in computer science, and I&#039;ve never used Facebook, Myspace, Twitter, LinkedIn, any smartphone, etc. It&#039;s mostly because I have no friends in real life whatsover. (And you don&#039;t need to tell me how important friends are for &quot;networking&quot;, I know).  I don&#039;t like technology today, but it was different when I grew up. Would it be weird for me to go for a tech job if I don&#039;t use today&#039;s technology? 

I remember at my last job which I was laid off from, I overheard someone talk about someone&#039;s resume (job wasn&#039;t tech related) which listed &quot;I use Facebook&quot; and that person said, &quot;duh, I use Facebook too&quot;. I also remember a coworker not being as friendly with me but brighten up when he saw someone he saw on LinkedIn, who then talked about how passionate he was about his expertise in computers (I have neither passion nor expertise). 

Honestly, I&#039;m sick of Web 2.0, it reminds me of high school, when I had &quot;friends&quot; aka bullies who asked me why I had only 1 friend (now 0). I know not all jobs are web related but what if I incidentally get asked to add a Facebook link to a web page, and then the employer says &quot;what? How can you never use Facebook? Everyone in their 20s uses it.&quot; and proceeds to fire me. Is there an alternative career I can go into, and would I need to go back to school for it?
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-27 20:33:47</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269747227</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100327203347AAJ3m9Z</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>ALsipB0daa</UserId>
    <UserNick>eternus</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1C9anL56qAAEC_AET3tB7Cg==.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I feel the same way, I don&#039;t want my potential employers to judge me on how many friends I have online. Unfortunately I do believe that is where things are headed now a days. Instead of Facebook use Linkedin or Zoominfo. It has a more professional appearance and requires little maintenance. It&#039;s important to market yourself, and that is how head hunters find you and offer you positions without you even actively searching. Still not convinced? Pick up some of the Guerrilla Marketing  for Job Hunters Book by Jay Conrad Levinson. That&#039;s what got me on board.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>e8ipTefGaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>KimbaQueen</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269935417</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1270083693</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I feel the same way, I don&#039;t want my potential employers to judge me on how many friends I have online. Unfortunately I do believe that is where things are headed now a days. Instead of Facebook use Linkedin or Zoominfo. It has a more professional appearance and requires little maintenance. It&#039;s important to market yourself, and that is how head hunters find you and offer you positions without you even actively searching. Still not convinced? Pick up some of the Guerrilla Marketing  for Job Hunters Book by Jay Conrad Levinson. That&#039;s what got me on board.</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.amazon.com/Guerrilla-Marketing-Job-Hunters-Unconventional/dp/0470455845/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;s=books&amp;qid=1269935351&amp;sr=1-1</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>e8ipTefGaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>KimbaQueen</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-30 00:50:17</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269935417</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws01.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:21:01 PDT 2010 -->
