<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100330195340AAvFh5r" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Dose Penguin Storm cause a virus?</Subject>
    <Content>For club penguin, there is the website called penguin storm, it&#039;s a cheat site. you can download it and log on to club penguin, and choose what you want then you have it. i really need to know if it hacks your account, or downloads a virus. i want 1,000,000 coins, and the beta hat... so im officially a super collector... please help! and if you download it, can you delete it from your computers memory forever? Thank-you so much! i &lt;3 U! :)
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-30 19:53:40</Date>
    <Timestamp>1270004020</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100330195340AAvFh5r</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>QQATjzTlaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Amy</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1sbRE2MVcAAEDhmOccKa1KEEFMA==.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Penguin Storm is a very cool program and a new version comes out at least every month. It will also remind you when I knew version is out, which is pretty cool. The current latest one is Penguin Storm 11. You can download it simply and doesn&#039;t cause any harm to your computer. There is rumors that he bans your penguin forever but I can tell you that that rumor is 100% NOT true. 

You can collect many coins on Penguin storm by Using &#039;Money Maker&#039; and you can make bots, make every penguin turn into a puffle and much more. I can tell you that my penguin is very rich now that I use Penguin Storm. 

Also, I hate to burst your bubble but you cannot collect the beta hat on Penguin Storm. You can collect it and have it on your penguin but is only visible on your screen and it won&#039;t show to other penguins. Also, when you log off and on Penguin storm, the beta hat will be gone. It will not stay in your penguin inventory, which I think, Is a bummer.

Good Luck :) Rate this best answer if it helped you :-)</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>vXu3eLIQaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Katie</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1270055614</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1270074209</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>No, it does not cause a virus. I had scanned my computer when I downloaded it and it didn&#039;t cause a virus. It&#039;s a very fun program. You can do many things on it such as using &quot;Money Maker&quot; or wear about any clothes that have been on club penguin in the past. It doesn&#039;t hack your account either and yes, you can remove it completely off your computers memory. Hope you have fun with it if you download it. Good Luck :)</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>O0hJxs9Eaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Cotton Candie</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-30 20:04:54</Date>
            <Timestamp>1270004694</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Penguin Storm is a very cool program and a new version comes out at least every month. It will also remind you when I knew version is out, which is pretty cool. The current latest one is Penguin Storm 11. You can download it simply and doesn&#039;t cause any harm to your computer. There is rumors that he bans your penguin forever but I can tell you that that rumor is 100% NOT true. 

You can collect many coins on Penguin storm by Using &#039;Money Maker&#039; and you can make bots, make every penguin turn into a puffle and much more. I can tell you that my penguin is very rich now that I use Penguin Storm. 

Also, I hate to burst your bubble but you cannot collect the beta hat on Penguin Storm. You can collect it and have it on your penguin but is only visible on your screen and it won&#039;t show to other penguins. Also, when you log off and on Penguin storm, the beta hat will be gone. It will not stay in your penguin inventory, which I think, Is a bummer.

Good Luck :) Rate this best answer if it helped you :-)</Content>
            <Reference>Club Penguin Cheats Websites, Google Research and Of Course, the Club Penguin Team Themselves.</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>vXu3eLIQaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Katie</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-31 10:13:34</Date>
            <Timestamp>1270055614</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws13.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:13:29 PDT 2010 -->
