<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100304140036AAutoAe" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Why does everything on lockerz.com say &quot;more soon&quot;???</Subject>
    <Content>Why does everything on lockerz.com say &quot;more soon&quot;?????? I want to redeem and everything is &quot;more soon&quot;
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-04 14:00:36</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267740036</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100304140036AAutoAe</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>f0jmkCe4aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>some dude</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Cuz they&#039;re a lame outfit?</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>gUNX2AdTaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>vmanes</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267740431</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268765148</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Cuz they&#039;re a lame outfit?</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.lockerz.com/faq  see item 6</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>gUNX2AdTaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>vmanes</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 14:07:11</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267740431</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>It’s a scam. I was a member of lockerz for 3 months and never got a thing. I ordered an ipod nano and it NEVER came. I called the company and asked them to give me a refund but they would not do it. Don&#039;t trust them it’s a scam! I found points2shop and its way better.

Points2shop is by far the best site for earning free cash/prizes. I&#039;ve been a member of all the get free stuff websites: Prizerebel, Swagbucks, Lockerz, Rewards1, and cashcrate. They were all really hard to earn points on. It was very time consuming. And I never got anything from those sites.

If I were you I&#039;d go to points2shop. You can earn points so easily on points2shop by completing offers, surveys, playing games, or simply by clicking on links! It’s that easy! I just received an ipod nano from points2shop in the mail last month. You get all your prizes directly off amazon.com, which makes shopping for prizes a lot easier because amazon has every item you could possibly want. 

Points2shop is best, fastest, and easiest site for getting free stuff. Best of all Points2shop is 100% free.If you need to know more information you can check their forums where members post the things that they have received for earning points on the points2shop website below.

The only way to get 250 free bonus points is by going to the link below and signing up.

http://www.points2shop.com/?ref=salibu</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>x8xgpyLQaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>thom</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-05 09:29:38</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267810178</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>They choose a random dates for the redemption&#039;s I suggest you to use LockerzAlerts - http://www.lockerzalerts.com  service , they will send you text message to your mobile phone when the redemption occurs ! its also FREE !</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>etgqPHdQaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>John</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-07 11:27:40</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267990060</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws09.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:10:04 PDT 2010 -->
