<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100302055510AAFXjwD" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Why isn&#039;t my Internet Explorer working?</Subject>
    <Content>So make a long story short, I have had the Flock browser for a while now and I never really used Internet Explorer.  I would be able to connect with it though and still use it if I had to.  Now, I recently downloaded Mozilla from Flock and it didn&#039;t work, so I uninstalled it.  I was going to try to use IE to download Mozilla again, but now it just says &quot;Diagnose Connection Problems&quot; when I&#039;m connected fine. It won&#039;t work at all, and I&#039;m not sure what the problem is... Help?
One more question... what would be considered funky settings and how could I check my firewall? I&#039;m not really experienced with this. lol
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-02 05:55:10</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267538110</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100302055510AAFXjwD</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>FTv1DeO9aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>ij;ouahsjdkfahsdkfas</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>2</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>check your avialable space, defragmentor page will tell you exactly how much space you have, and add/remove programs will let you make more, and do the disk clean up</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>Z4sH97Vcaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>mr.dfleming57</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267541231</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268057611</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Assuming its not something silly like say, IE needs to be reinstalled; check the IE settings- make sure that it doesn&#039;t have some funky settings, or the firewall is blocking it.

Worst case, download FF on another computer, copy to flash drive, install to computer from there (maybe retain a copy of the installer just in case you have to install it again)</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>wPsVEsWRaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>jared_e42</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-02 06:00:38</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267538438</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>check your avialable space, defragmentor page will tell you exactly how much space you have, and add/remove programs will let you make more, and do the disk clean up</Content>
            <Reference>me</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>Z4sH97Vcaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>mr.dfleming57</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-02 06:47:11</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267541231</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>If ur using a laptop check the wireless switch, if ur using windows such as vista, u should have a bar on top of ur desktop, make sure one of the lights is switched on deppending what conncetion u have.

Microsoft has been ordered this week to give all its european users who are using vista, xp and 7 an option of 12 different internet browsers, 5 main ones will be IE, Firefox, G Chrome, Opera and Safari, u&#039;ll also get another 7 less known options, it will apear in a pop up starting this week, That may be the reason why its slow,</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>L8Tbnc9raa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Shinobi</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-02 07:11:57</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267542717</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
        <Comment>
            <Content></Content>
            <UserId>Z4sH97Vcaa</UserId>
            <UserNick></UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 06:49:15</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267542717</Timestamp>
        </Comment>
        <Comment>
            <Content></Content>
            <UserId>Z4sH97Vcaa</UserId>
            <UserNick></UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 08:31:09</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267542717</Timestamp>
        </Comment>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws08.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:27:09 PDT 2010 -->
