<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100308234152AAzOGUv" type="Answered">
    <Subject>What is a better free stuff site lockerz, swagbucks or Points2shop?</Subject>
    <Content>Im about to start one of them up and im just wondering whats site earns you prizes faster and still keeps it legit, or if you know a site thats better, i just dont want any credit card BS yah know, and i dont want have to buy other things from other sites to earn points.
Thank you all very much for taking your time on my question .:.
:)   
(:
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-08 23:41:52</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268120512</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100308234152AAzOGUv</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>nTcb5o0Caa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Demsokk</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>1. Lockerz, earn points by 2&#039;s or 4&#039;s. Redemtpion: 5 minutes, once a month
2. Swagbucks, earn points by 10&#039;s-100&#039;. Redemption: 24/7.
3.Points2Shop Must complete offers, very annoying.


I recommend swagbucks wayyy more.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>n4bgt38Paa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Sidrit</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268147830</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268182003</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I use swagbucks and it seems to work nicely. Ive had lockerz but it has too many problems. Never heards of Points2shop. ill try it though</Content>
            <Reference>I recommend swagbucks</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>12aQ3ZNFaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Gabby </UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 23:47:48</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268120868</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Well, I have not tried p2s so cannot comment there But as far as lockerz or swagbucks. I have kept an eye on lockerz&#039;s members on their facebook wall and everyone was complaining that there their gifts are always out of stock. and when they stock, they&#039;re gone in few minutes.
My suggestion is to sign up for swagbucks if you want to earn money for searching, I signed up for it about 3 months ago. Unlike lockerz, swagbucks makes it easy to earn bucks and more importantly redeemable bucks.
My favorites are the $5 amazon cards and $5 payapl credit.
I have signed up about 3 months ago and have $25 in my amazon account and I am not a heavy user. I am also saving for christmas shopping on amazon this year.. (Do not like Mall crowds :))
Here is a link to sign up:
http://www.swagbucks.com/refer/hnks

Use it for your daily searches. Here is my recommendation to get more points.
In the morning, search on swagbucks, wait 30 seconds and search again, and so on until you get bucks, then wait for 2-3 hours and repeat till you get bucks and so on.
Also watch the swidget because almost every day, they post a code for extr bucks.
And lastly, check the special offers page for videos to watch and get more bucks..</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>d6E8i3dUaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>HNK</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-09 06:43:31</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268145811</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>1. Lockerz, earn points by 2&#039;s or 4&#039;s. Redemtpion: 5 minutes, once a month
2. Swagbucks, earn points by 10&#039;s-100&#039;. Redemption: 24/7.
3.Points2Shop Must complete offers, very annoying.


I recommend swagbucks wayyy more.</Content>
            <Reference>I have experience from all those sites, and I think you should use swagbucks better.</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>n4bgt38Paa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Sidrit</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-09 07:17:10</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268147830</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws01.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:27:38 PDT 2010 -->
