<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100325220141AAIN6GI" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Is my Roommate stealing the wireless internet?</Subject>
    <Content>All of the sudden the internet that has been shared among 4 of us roommates for months (flawlessly) is only working well for my one roommate.

She is the &quot;techy&quot; in our group and set up the internet in the first place. 

When we try to tell her that it&#039;s not working for us, she replies in a manner clearing stating that she doesn&#039;t care saying &quot;It works fine for me!&quot; 

Could my roommate have sabotaged our internet to work best for her?

She and my other roommate connect with a cable while my boyfriend and I use wireless (all from the same router) however the only one getting ANY internet speed/efficiency at all is her.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-25 22:01:41</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269579701</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100325220141AAIN6GI</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>ooJUnBP8aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>curry2386</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://avatars.zenfs.com/users/1UwBF1HK_AAIB9IFD6JjlJJ4A.medium.png</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Does your speed decrease only when she is connected and is using the shared bandwidth or do you have the problem all the time? If this problem appears only when she comes online and start using the net, then she could have done something to limit your bandwidth (I cannot say that for sure) but if you have the problem all the time you should search for the cause somewhere else .

But again I cannot say that for sure because I need more details. Computer and Internet are complicated and a problem can have many different reasons. I suggest you to ask a tech-savvy friend to check your system.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>HjEEKVdmaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Net Expert</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269581407</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269623112</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>she could have yes, but i beleive that shes getteing betetr internet because shes using a WIRED connection

wireless is alot harder to connect, when with a wire its plugged right in so you will have less problems</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>v6GZtU3caa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Andrew</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-25 22:05:01</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269579901</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Does your speed decrease only when she is connected and is using the shared bandwidth or do you have the problem all the time? If this problem appears only when she comes online and start using the net, then she could have done something to limit your bandwidth (I cannot say that for sure) but if you have the problem all the time you should search for the cause somewhere else .

But again I cannot say that for sure because I need more details. Computer and Internet are complicated and a problem can have many different reasons. I suggest you to ask a tech-savvy friend to check your system.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>4</Best>
            <UserId>HjEEKVdmaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Net Expert</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-25 22:30:07</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269581407</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I think the main problem is that your roomate seems like a nasty person, and I&#039;d be looking to move away from her if at all possible.  If you had a nice roommate you trusted, would you have to ask a question like this?  You will be much happier if you gewt away from her in my opinion, regardless of what&#039;s going on with the internet.  I&#039;d bet there&#039;s other problems there also.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>zQhuE0qaaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>csss s</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-26 08:04:57</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269615897</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws14.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:28:37 PDT 2010 -->
