<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100303100925AAO5aT1" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Should I delete my formspring? Can&#039;t decide. Best answer. :)?</Subject>
    <Content>I can&#039;t decide if I should delete my formspring.me account. I am a blogger and a lot of the people I talk with have one and regardless if they delete theirs, I will do what I want. However, I kinda gave it a trial run. It&#039;s not a horrible site and I haven&#039;t been harassed or anything, but I see it happen all the time. I find it kinda like by signing up and answering questions your just waiting for something to happen. And honestly, I don&#039;t see the point in it, if someone needs to ask me something important they will either at me on twitter, email me, or comment my blog. On top of it all, the site has tons of spam. Not just here or there, tons. Like twitter. Speaking of twitter, honestly I don&#039;t even see the point in that site as well. Who gives a crap what your doing, it kinda annoys me to hear about what people are doing. Same with facebook but that is a whole different bucket of crap, that is family involved and they made me sign up. I never go on it. Matter of fact, I crap canned that along time ago but a family member made me sign up for it again. However, twitter is a big part of my blogging and I don&#039;t want to delete that, that would be a loss to my blog. I mean, by what I say should I delete my formspring? I&#039;m confused and stressed about this, lol.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-03 10:09:25</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267639765</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100303100925AAO5aT1</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>RZ9HgX0Oaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>F-A-S-H-I-O-N</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://avatars.zenfs.com/users/1H8DbaJM7AAEC-KFBvAynOBi3LQ==.medium.png</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I would if I were you.  If you want to be able to post blogs, videos and pics and actually have people notice them check out then you should try this site.  The community is very respectful and they always comment and give feedback

http://vloggerzoo.ning.com 

it&#039;s is a really good site for that</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>QP1T81yRaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Justagirl</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267831418</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268159191</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I think you should delete it because you say it serves you no purpose as there are alternative ways of people asking you questions and although you haven&#039;t been harassed yet, you easily could be in the future. Don&#039;t stress about it haha, I know what you mean though because I am seriously contemplating deleting my facebook grrr!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>RcVSPsHPaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>afterthestorm</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-03 10:12:35</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267639955</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I would if I were you.  If you want to be able to post blogs, videos and pics and actually have people notice them check out then you should try this site.  The community is very respectful and they always comment and give feedback

http://vloggerzoo.ning.com 

it&#039;s is a really good site for that</Content>
            <Reference>http://vloggerzoo.ning.com</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>QP1T81yRaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Justagirl</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-05 15:23:38</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267831418</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws04.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:18:21 PDT 2010 -->
