<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100303054923AAAXNJ3" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Question about a website called the pirate bay?</Subject>
    <Content>A friend of mine uses this site all the time.  I&#039;m seen some of the movies he&#039;s downloaded and they are really crappy quality.  It looked like someone just went into a movie theater and used a camcorder.  How can he get caught?  I&#039;m sure this is totally illegal.  For me, I&#039;d rather wait until it comes out to dvd that way the quality will be much better.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-03 05:49:23</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267624163</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100303054923AAAXNJ3</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>c3e7d0770e820edfde95efa81b756399aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>star77</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Once the movie comes out on DVD, your friend can download a DVD rip that&#039;s as good quality as what you&#039;re paying for. Why do you want him to get caught?</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>Qp0u9q5Naa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Emmy</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267624306</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268385133</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Once the movie comes out on DVD, your friend can download a DVD rip that&#039;s as good quality as what you&#039;re paying for. Why do you want him to get caught?</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>Qp0u9q5Naa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Emmy</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-03 05:51:46</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267624306</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I would never report somebody for downloading illegally but I would try and convince him is is not the smartest thing to do.  There is a chance his ISP might be monitoring illegal downloads.
Do you know movies aren&#039; available for (free) download?
It is because it is the money made from sales (DVD&#039;s etc.) of cvurrent movies that provides the money to make new movies.
Too many people have the bizarre notion that the Internet is some sort of magical free place, when in fact the normal real-life rules of commerce and retailing still apply.
If you created items to sell, you would not allow total strangers to simply take them for free - otherwise you&#039;d have no money to create new items.
Illegal downloaders are either incredibly naive or unbelievably selfish - a slowdown in new releases will affect everybody, not just those who caused it</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>2LbTrlQnaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>JIM</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-03 06:00:05</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267624805</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I heard people in the film industry put treasure underneath the seat and place treasure maps in big billboards outside the cinema. Once they sit down and put their fingers into the chest. BOOM ! A mouse trap goes off.


Those bloody pirates &gt;.&gt;</Content>
            <Reference>Spell checker</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>vtmVhqVhaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Lenny</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-03 06:02:02</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267624922</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws01.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:19:36 PDT 2010 -->
