<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100306093830AAUjPDN" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Refund issue on ebay ?</Subject>
    <Content>I recently bought a hat to discover it was fake, I was annoyed and threw it away as I didn&#039;t have use for it. I asked him for a refund because it was pathetic and now he is asking for the hat to be returned for a refund. Surely thats illegal anyways but i havent got the hat. I also accepted a case he opened saying the tranasaction has been cancelled, although I have already paid for it ? and the transasction is complete. I can&#039;t be bothered to deal with the hassle, but would like to know what is going on with the case. Does it mean I will receive my money back or not
It should be different because fake items are representations of the real item and is an infringement of copyright, which can damage business sales. When trading standards obtain fake items they make sure they are destroyed. By returning a fake item back to a seller, I am just gonna put someone else in my situation
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-06 09:38:30</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267897110</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100306093830AAUjPDN</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>F0DjGdt2aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Max</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>If you threw it away and then asked for a refund, you&#039;re pretty much out of luck. If you went to a store and bought something and didn&#039;t like it, threw it away and then went back to the store and wanted a refund - you wouldn&#039;t get one. So why would this situation be any different?</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>WXdkmSbDaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>*EmmaSurella*</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267897705</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268416552</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>If you threw it away and then asked for a refund, you&#039;re pretty much out of luck. If you went to a store and bought something and didn&#039;t like it, threw it away and then went back to the store and wanted a refund - you wouldn&#039;t get one. So why would this situation be any different?</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>WXdkmSbDaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>*EmmaSurella*</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 09:48:25</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267897705</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws08.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:48:39 PDT 2010 -->
