<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100307155242AAPPdK2" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Where can I learn about making money online?</Subject>
    <Content>
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-07 15:52:42</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268005962</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100307155242AAPPdK2</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>XbNJJ4rAaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>justthatguy</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>11</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Can&#039;t say much whether it works or not but from my experience I have seen so many people regret wasting a lot of money online yet still can&#039;t earn any money online. and the one that has made money online from my observation has been online for a long time before ever make good money and most of them are already somebody in the offline world. The had full time job before but couldn&#039;t stand to work 9-5 jobs anymore so they tried to find something online.

Basically I can say if you want to earn money online you need to have some of kind of expertise and credibility because I also found that most people buy from people they trust. and even more so now than before. credibility and trustworthy is very critical online. just take a look at you. how long would you take to make the decision to make a purchase? Do you really believe strangers giving you some answer to your questions right away.

Most people don&#039;t even realise this. they took time to make a purchase but when they sell something they expect people to buy from them the first time those people came across their website. so please understand the reality of internet first and you will know how to make online. and it would be a little bit easier if you really have the desire. hope that helps a bit.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>JiP4TbR8aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Rikol</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268060934</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268525651</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I&#039;ve recently found a great forum to learn about this type of thing.  It&#039;s called the Internet Money Maker forums.  It&#039;s a cool community.  Maybe you&#039;ll enjoy it too! 

http://immforums.com/forum/index.php?referrerid=881</Content>
            <Reference>http://immforums.com/forum/index.php?referrerid=881</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>pMqqQ7Pcaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>coolcow</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-07 15:54:15</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268006055</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Google.


http://answers.yahoo.com/question/index;_ylt=Aj1On2pZL07C_mVtM5mo_G3sy6IX;_ylv=3?qid=20100307152248AAmJtRA</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>3khh4ieAaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>tomboy91135</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-07 15:57:25</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268006245</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Google just gives you random sites... but I know a good site where you can make money online. It&#039;s called Cashle. You earn money by completing simple offers where all you have to do is give your e-mail or fill out surveys. It&#039;s really easy and I already made some money. If you sign up from the link below you can message me anytime if you need help because when I first signed up I know I was confused and the people from the site wouldn&#039;t answer ALL my questions.  Hope you give the site a try. :)
They give pay outs daily and there&#039;s no minimum like some other sites.

*** The person above me didn&#039;t answer truthfully because you CANNOT make MONEY by playing games on Cashle, that&#039;s only on Points2Shop, which gives POINTS for playing games. Also the daily clicks are GONE, so that&#039;s not even an option anymore. Cashle only gives money for offers and surveys.</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.cashle.com/?ref=somechicky</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>FZIN7OHKaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Miss</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-07 16:23:10</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268007790</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>There are many good work from home jobs and there are many good home based businesses. A job is one where someone will pay you to do their work at home. A home based business is one where you&#039;ll earn commissions for running a business from home. If you&#039;re just looking to be paid for your services, do your research...you have to know the type of job you want to do, then look for companies that offer that type of job.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>FH5uvUpmaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>j wale</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-07 19:36:21</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268019381</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Like yourself I&#039;v been searching for quite awhile for a good work at home job but to no avail. All I can say is there are alot of scams out there and just be carefull. Any real work from home job will never ask for a fee upfront so dont even waste your money trying. Take it from me I&#039;v lost quite alot trying. Remember if it seems to good to be true then it probably is!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>Pd1mP5Pzaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Happiness is Within Everyone</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-07 23:25:11</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268033111</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Why not start your own thing, get a site, add some adverts and drive traffic to it :
there&#039;s some free vids at:
http://bestinternetfind.solutionsarticles.com/free-work-from-home-help.html</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>VYiWWgNRaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>rogers</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 00:35:20</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268037320</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>visit my site 4 online jobs. 100% free to join with genuine payments. For more details...
visit my site &amp; blogs
http://darshi.webs.com
http://sridarshika.blogspot.com
http://darshiprakash.blogspot.com</Content>
            <Reference>http://darshi.webs.com</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>2GMZLUWoaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>darshi</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 03:02:37</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268046157</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Can&#039;t say much whether it works or not but from my experience I have seen so many people regret wasting a lot of money online yet still can&#039;t earn any money online. and the one that has made money online from my observation has been online for a long time before ever make good money and most of them are already somebody in the offline world. The had full time job before but couldn&#039;t stand to work 9-5 jobs anymore so they tried to find something online.

Basically I can say if you want to earn money online you need to have some of kind of expertise and credibility because I also found that most people buy from people they trust. and even more so now than before. credibility and trustworthy is very critical online. just take a look at you. how long would you take to make the decision to make a purchase? Do you really believe strangers giving you some answer to your questions right away.

Most people don&#039;t even realise this. they took time to make a purchase but when they sell something they expect people to buy from them the first time those people came across their website. so please understand the reality of internet first and you will know how to make online. and it would be a little bit easier if you really have the desire. hope that helps a bit.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>JiP4TbR8aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Leaded Gas</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 07:08:54</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268060934</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Most of the answers here will be rambling balls of spam and scams; so watch what you click on.

The only three things that have worked for me:

1) GPTHQ (the best free GPT site I&#039;ve ever used)

2) eBay (the fees are a bit much but still good)

3) Google Adsense (if you have a blog or website with some OK traffic)

Hope these help; links in source :)</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.gpthq.com
http://ebay.com
http://google.com/adsense

Also - http://blog.gpthq.com - that has some great advice if you&#039;re new to GPT.
OR - http://answernode.com - a forum that has some other ideas on it.</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>mvuYfUgNaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Juno</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 12:57:48</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268081868</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Step 1: Open a paypal account.
Step 2: Use a credit card to verify your paypal account.(optional)
Step 3: Join the world of Paid Surveys, Paid to Click and Paid to Read. These websites are free to register and within a month you start earning. Slowly but steadily your money grows and you get a payout. Sooner than you think you get another payout and this continues as long as you click. 
Step 4: When you reach a minimum payout you may encash to your paypal account or rent referrals (who earn for you) and encash later when you have a good balance.
Step 5: Eventually you transfer the amount to paypal and then to your bank account. You can also use the paypal earnings for online shopping.
There are a lot of scams over the net so I am giving a few websites that ACTUALLY PAY. I use them  and they really work.

PAID TO CLICK
============
NEOBUX - WORLD&#039;S BEST PTC. guaranteed payout, no scam
http://www.neobux.com/?r=gbanerji

OLEBUX - payout guaranteed, no scam
http://www.olebux.com/register.php/gbanerji.html

OMNIBUX - payout guaranteed, no scam
http://www.omnibux.com/?r=gbanerji
PAID TO READ
===========
Getor- Mails - takes time for 1st payout, Please read TOS carefully since they dont really pay 200$ for reading a mail. 200$ is like 200 points :) After 1st payment you get a consistant earning.
http://www.getor-mails.com/pages/index.php?refid=gbanerji
PAID SURVEYS
============
AWSurveys - Take surveys and get money, requires patience and referrals.
http://www.AWSurveys.com/HomeMain.cfm?RefID=gaurab_banerji

PAID TO CLICK + INVEST
===================
JM&amp;GOLD - Invest 25$ on silver bar and get back 5$ monthly + get a silver bar for 1000 click and more, strategy is to keep clicking on ads and you will be able to buy 1 silver bar in 2 months, from then onwards you get 5$ monthly doing nothing, You can continue woking to increase your income. No limits thereof.
http://www.jmgold.com/?ref=gbanerji

Guys I need your support on this, So please keep my referral id intact while you register. :)</Content>
            <Reference>http://gaurab.2ya.com</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>AA11775378</UserId>
            <UserNick>gaurab_banerji</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-10 01:58:36</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268215116</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Hi there,
I work for 2 different company&#039;s that allow you to work from home. One of them I have just recently joined and the other I have been working with for just over 1 month and I am actually making money!. Both of them include full training.
If you would like more information on them, please email me at pstrachan-07@hotmail.co.uk
Paul Strachan</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>NPsco2qRaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Paul</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-11 10:09:09</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268330949</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws13.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:37:20 PDT 2010 -->
