<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100223110308AA7eouB" type="Answered">
    <Subject>is it a bad idea to buy a .co.uk domain if the .com version is taken but not being used?</Subject>
    <Content>
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-23 11:03:08</Date>
    <Timestamp>1266951788</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100223110308AA7eouB</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>fxpbmsxmaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>¢σяя вℓιмєу</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/4b1d487bi43bzul4re4/luYjc8oydLRzndUiFt1jl0kptA--/4/tn48.jpg?ciAAToMBsBAEnAwg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>No, it&#039;s a good idea if you are a company dealing primarily in the UK!  

     I am often frustrated by searching for car-parts online, and then getting a response, e.g. &quot;Clutch specialists in Hampshire&quot;, will give me a load of results, I might be reading one that seems ok, and then find it is in New Hampshire, the prices are in dollars, they don&#039;t have parts for my car, and arrgghh, I want companies near me in England!</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>AA11900069</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Please punctuate properly folks.</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1266952017</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267135326</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>No, it&#039;s a good idea if you are a company dealing primarily in the UK!  

     I am often frustrated by searching for car-parts online, and then getting a response, e.g. &quot;Clutch specialists in Hampshire&quot;, will give me a load of results, I might be reading one that seems ok, and then find it is in New Hampshire, the prices are in dollars, they don&#039;t have parts for my car, and arrgghh, I want companies near me in England!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>3</Best>
            <UserId>AA11900069</UserId>
            <UserNick>Please punctuate properly folks.</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-23 11:06:57</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266952017</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>If I were you I tried to find a .com domain name which is more popular. People more memorize com extension.

Take into consideration that web hosting is a global service. It does not matter what country you are located in; US, UK, Canada, Australia or India. It is good to note that the cost of hosting services in most countries is generally a little more expensive in comparison to the same services in Canada and the United States. Specifically, American web hosts offer a much better value for money than any local hosting.

If you want to start your website I recommend purchase your domain and hosting together. In this way it is possible to get your domain for free. Some hosting services offer this gift today.

As an experienced webmaster I recommend BH web hosting which I’m sure it would work for you and fulfill all your requirements. They have a really great offer for hosting &amp; I have used them for over 3 yrs now, and have never had a single problem with them. 

You can reach reviews about this web hosting provider and its latest DISCOUNT COUPONS at:


http://www.threehosts.com/reviews/1st

Only $3.95 /month (with discount coupon).

******IMPORTANT********
* This service was awarded the “Best Web Hosting OF The Year”.
* If you sign up for this service you will have $75 credits to advertise your website with the google &amp; yahoo search engines for free!
* You Can Register A Free Domain or Use Your Existing Domains. They Support All Domain Names.
****************************
Hope this helps.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>MVr0vbbNaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>David M</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-24 10:41:23</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267036883</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws05.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 02:20:30 PDT 2010 -->
