<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100313145800AA6yBHk" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Why are quite a few of my friends being deleted?</Subject>
    <Content>It seems like on facebook, messengers, and my phone there are people being deleted or removed. For the couple of months, there has been at least one contact being deleted every week. Every now and then, I would notice that someone has been deleted from my facebook and I nor the other person removed me from their friends. Even from other sites like myspace and yahoo and aim, there has been just people getting deleted. I&#039;m able to get back some of them but others are just lost. What is causing this and why? Is it just technical malfuntions? Is it people who are somehow accessing my stuff and deleting people for no reason?
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-13 14:58:00</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268521080</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100313145800AA6yBHk</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>F5AHLuxnaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>alexja1118</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/102gxQXjqAAEC_AFGcGE=.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Forget what Chloe said, what a stupid thing to say.  The only explanation I can think of is that people decide to delete their account for some reason or the provider deletes them for some reason.  They could be deleted because they are violating the terms of use or for some other reason.  Don&#039;t worry about people getting into your accounts and I don&#039;t think it&#039;s technical as much as just that people either delte themselves or get deleted.  

Why don&#039;t you find someone at school who was deleted from your facebook and ask them about it.  They will probably say they deleted so they could change their screen name or something. There could be a lot of reasons, but it isn&#039;t your fault.  Good luck.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>ddWK5JRKaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Rob R</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268532852</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268762467</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>no, this can totally be fixed!

what you do is press Alt and F4, whilst saying (one of) the name(s) of the removed contact(s). if you do this correctly, the page should not close. keep trying though if, on the first few times, it does. it&#039;s maybe best to practice on other documents, like an essay - it HAS to be not saved, otherwise it doesn&#039;t work - and apply the formula to get used to it.

good luck!</Content>
            <Reference>they&#039;re probably deleting you.</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>oial0OcQaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Chloe</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-13 15:17:11</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268522231</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Forget what Chloe said, what a stupid thing to say.  The only explanation I can think of is that people decide to delete their account for some reason or the provider deletes them for some reason.  They could be deleted because they are violating the terms of use or for some other reason.  Don&#039;t worry about people getting into your accounts and I don&#039;t think it&#039;s technical as much as just that people either delte themselves or get deleted.  

Why don&#039;t you find someone at school who was deleted from your facebook and ask them about it.  They will probably say they deleted so they could change their screen name or something. There could be a lot of reasons, but it isn&#039;t your fault.  Good luck.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>3</Best>
            <UserId>ddWK5JRKaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Rob R</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-13 18:14:12</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268532852</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws13.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:02:50 PDT 2010 -->
