<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100228224729AAGC0rv" type="Answered">
    <Subject>I am looking for a new internet provider similar to Cricket, with no contract &amp; no Credit Check.  Any advice?</Subject>
    <Content>I currently have Cricket Internet 3G as my Provider.  I am not happy with the Customer Service with receive when we have a problem.  I would like to find a similar company to switch to.  I am looking for a service with no contract &amp; no credit check.  I do not have a home phone line.  Any ideas?
Thank you Ryan.  I drive from another county to pay my Cricket phone &amp; internet when I have a problem.  I can never seem to get help over the phone so I end up driving.  The reps in store have been the worst Customer service reps I have ever seen, in any business.  The only reason I have stayed is because I do like the internet service itself.  I can get a phone anywhere.  I have often been told 1 thing by 1 rep &amp; then the very next visit been told something completely different.  I have been over charged &amp; refused a refund, I have bought insurance on my broadband card &amp; then when it broke, was told I didn&#039;t have it.  Luckily, my Dad gave me an old card to use.  When this one breaks, I will have to go else where.  My phone has been converted to a Cricket because I really loved my phone &amp; didn&#039;t want to purchase another.  Now, it gives me problems with texting more often than not.  Sorry to sound bitchy, it just seems I always dread having to deal with these reps.  Thanks for offering!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-28 22:47:29</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267426049</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100228224729AAGC0rv</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>ZXaupWxNaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>anglsm</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>with 3g will be rough.  Metropcs has no contract and internet, but i dont think that they do 3g</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>PX2uuH2taa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Chris</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267576574</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268322805</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>with 3g will be rough.  Metropcs has no contract and internet, but i dont think that they do 3g</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>PX2uuH2taa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Chris</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-02 16:36:14</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267576574</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Hi Anglsm,

My name is Ryan and I work in partnership with Cricket. Is there any specific service issues you have been experiencing that we may help answer for you. We would love to help you by providing a customer service rep. that would be more than happy to help.

Thanks,
Ryan on behalf of Cricket</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>5mbkhuuYaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Ryan C</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 09:59:04</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267725544</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws14.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:34:07 PDT 2010 -->
