<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100306105303AAwBs7e" type="Answered">
    <Subject>What is your take and review on the website Chat Roulette?</Subject>
    <Content>I heard about Chat Roulette on the Daily Show- and when John  Stewart suggested there were a lot of &#039;free floating dongs&#039; on that site, he was understating things-
I explored site for 3 hours yesterday and found very little  evidence of intelligent discussion- It was 90% pornographic 5% jerks who did nothing but insult me, 4 %  20-something guys cruising for hot women,and 1% interesting people ready to have intelligent discussion.

I thought the big reason so many people are rude and obnoxious on message boards boards is because they can hide behind their computer screen-but with this site, where your face invisible- I thought people would be at their best- but it&#039;s the opposite-

I think chat roulette has an aspect of communications  that will be commonplace in telecommunications in the next 10 years- I think within 10 years all telephones will have an interactive real time video component-- But Chat Roulette is pure anarchy.

I&#039;m not interested in seeing middle  aged guys whack  off, so i&#039;m not going back.

If you visited the site- what did you think. Does it have any redeeming qualities- or is it a free-for all freak show?
The segment on the Daily Show was frickin hilarious- John Stewart  was right, everytother person on ChatRoulette is some guy pounding his pud...
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-06 10:53:03</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267901583</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100306105303AAwBs7e</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>IC5hsNFzaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Crumb bum</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>You answered your own question. In two words, &quot;it&#039;s irresponsible.&quot; (I saw the same Jon Stewart show, it was funny, lol)</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>hpzjJ47Uaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>eric</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267901924</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268030258</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>You answered your own question. In two words, &quot;it&#039;s irresponsible.&quot; (I saw the same Jon Stewart show, it was funny, lol)</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>3</Best>
            <UserId>hpzjJ47Uaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>eric</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 10:58:44</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267901924</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws07.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:48:01 PDT 2010 -->
