<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100227154618AAX7wFZ" type="Answered">
    <Subject>How can i download files from sites like the piratebay.org  without getting caught by my internet provider?</Subject>
    <Content>How can i download files from the piratebay.org and other torrent sites without getting caught? A few months ago i was caught seeding a file by bethesda, which immediately notified charter (my internet provider) which sent me a PRE-lawsuit notice (it basically said that i got caught and if i did it again i would get sued.) about a month later my friend was visiting my house and his bitorrent client automatically began downloading some files. Less then an hour later we recieved another email, saying that this time was the last straw. So i know that charter is watching me, making sure i don&#039;t download anything, but i really want to be able to use the piratebay because it makes my life so much easier. DOES ANYBODY KNOW A WAY THAT I COULD GET AROUND THIS OR FIND ANOTHER WAY DO DOWNLOAD THE FILE OR SOMETHING???????!!!!!!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-27 15:46:18</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267314378</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100227154618AAX7wFZ</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>ka9QvdAcaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>goodwood</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>visit the site through a proxy provider website, just google search them ,</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>AdhCCSV8aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Luke</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267314649</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268102685</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>visit the site through a proxy provider website, just google search them ,</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>AdhCCSV8aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Luke</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-27 15:50:49</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267314649</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Please see the Yahoo Answer community guidelines concerning questions and answers involving breaking the law and illegal activities.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>td6WXhv4aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>mr.quix</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-28 14:23:56</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267395836</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws02.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:42:22 PDT 2010 -->
