<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100227080921AAQs6MG" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Does .info domains matter in Search engine rankings? (SEO)?</Subject>
    <Content>I plan to buy several .info domains because it is on sale on Godaddy for only $1.. Will it matter on my search engine? Is it really advantageous to use .coms or .info is fine.. I am hoping for some answers..i would appreciate it a lot..
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-27 08:09:21</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267286961</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100227080921AAQs6MG</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>H8Lv2nu8aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>christian</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://avatars.zenfs.com/users/1UdFYCWamAAQC_GH6kDLrBw==.medium.png</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Ill be honest. It ALL depends on content and SEO you apply. If Google likes your page and is relevant to your SEO keyword, it is the same thing. 

Some people will say that its better to buy com. And well, they might be right. 

But the fact that I can go out and do the same thing with 1$ .info domain than a 14$ .com domain, well you see my point. Its all about your work in the end. Now think what you want:
.com= true, this normally means higher chances to rank good
.info=WAY cheaper and if you know how to do it, its the same as a .com</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>0K6dHdB5aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Julijan T</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267287429</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267806298</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Ill be honest. It ALL depends on content and SEO you apply. If Google likes your page and is relevant to your SEO keyword, it is the same thing. 

Some people will say that its better to buy com. And well, they might be right. 

But the fact that I can go out and do the same thing with 1$ .info domain than a 14$ .com domain, well you see my point. Its all about your work in the end. Now think what you want:
.com= true, this normally means higher chances to rank good
.info=WAY cheaper and if you know how to do it, its the same as a .com</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>0K6dHdB5aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Julijan T</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-27 08:17:09</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267287429</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Don’t trust any cheap service, many of them don’t allow you to have full control on your domain name. If you’re going to buy domain names,  refer to:

http://www.goldpuma.com/

GoldPuma is the lowest cost service which is full-featured and really works for you ($9.99 /year). They offer free extras with every domain name:

Quick Blogcast
Hosting with Web site builder
Personalized Email Account
Starter Web Page For Sale/ Parked Page
Domain Parking
Domain Forwarding
Domain Masking
100-Pack Email Forwarding
Total DNS Control
Change of Registration
Status Alerts
Domain Locking
…

As you may know a domain name is just a name, not a real website. If you are going to create your website: 1- Buy a domain name. A domain name is a name you want to call your website (ex: www.yahoo.com).  To get a domain name, you have to pay an annual fee to a registrar for the right to use that name. 2- Buy a web hosting service to provide your online space and enable you to get your website online at your purchased domain name.

If you want to start your website I recommend purchase your domain and hosting together. In this way it is possible to get your domain for free. Some hosting services offer this gift today.

As an experienced webmaster I recommend BlueHost service which I’m sure it would work for you and fulfill all your requirements. They have a really great offer for hosting &amp; I have used them for over 3 yrs now, and have never had a single problem with them.

You can reach reviews about this web hosting provider and its latest DISCOUNT COUPONS at:

http://www.threehosts.com/reviews/1st

Only $3.95 /month (with discount coupon).

They also offer &quot;Free Site Builder&quot; that helps you build your web pages without difficulty if you are not skilled in using any website creating program. (WYSIWYG: What You See Is What You Get) You can use this service optionally. You can also create the pages offline with your favorite program (DreamWeaver, FrontPage, Microsoft Publisher, etc.), and then upload them to your web host. This is another easy way to get your website online.

******IMPORTANT*******
* This service was awarded the “Best Web Hosting OF The Year”.
* If you sign up for this service you will have $75 credits to advertise your website with the google &amp; yahoo search engines for free!
* You Can Register A Free Domain or Use Your Existing Domains. They Support All Domain Names.
**************************

Another useful link:
http://www.threehosts.com/build
There you can find a step-by-step guide to start your website.

And the lowest cost reputed service which is full-featured and really works for you  is available at:
http://www.threehosts.com/tell-me-more/pad.html
Only $1.99 /month (with discount coupon).

Hope this helps.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>MVr0vbbNaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>David M</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-27 10:50:19</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267296619</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws01.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:45:09 PDT 2010 -->
