<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100225180654AAHubf0" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Who hates lockerz  ?????????????</Subject>
    <Content>I hate that dumb lockerz. Its so gay. Ive been saving up to get a prize but no there was to much people on it and it couldnt log me on. Now its the second wave and i didnt buy it. I HATE IT LOCKERZ SO MUCH. ITS GAY AND RETARDED SO SLOW AND JUST GAY. Whatever if you guys ban my account go ahead. wait you guys dont know my email address so hah.ive been waiting so long but no i get this sorry your not in this wave. and what about the promise so you can only get one prize so every on can get something. Is everyone getting something? NO so whoever hates lockerz please agree and send this to every one you know. Please tell me why you hate it
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-25 18:06:54</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267150014</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100225180654AAHubf0</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>wuzI5d3gaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Alick</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>lmao noob, qq moar!</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>JQ2SHkuAaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Mr.Xu</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267150272</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268436284</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>lmao noob, qq moar!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>JQ2SHkuAaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Mr.Xu</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-25 18:11:12</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267150272</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I don&#039;t think they have ever really paid out in redemption.  I joined that site months ago and I am still waiting.  It&#039;s a scam.  Every time they SAY they have stuff in stock, it disappears before anyone can redeem it.  (very suspicious).  And this has happened 3 times already.

I would dump it if I were u.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>Y2LoZQlMaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Andrew Clements</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-25 18:12:51</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267150371</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Majority of people who actually claim they got something were either working for Lockerz or got the t-shirt which was a $1 shirt (at the most) that was free advertising for Lockerz so they just assume it&#039;s legit.  I don&#039;t doubt you can get prizes but they are VERY limited and Lockerz will try and screw you out of your PTZ anyways they can so they don&#039;t have to pay out.

Total scam = no
A waste of time = yes

Easier to work a few days and buy what you wanted with your own hard earned cash.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>9NO8q2Joaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>jdr</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-25 18:37:22</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267151842</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws06.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:54:33 PDT 2010 -->
