<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100321232723AAOefjT" type="Answered">
    <Subject>I was wondering how to make my games run better on roadrunner turbo?</Subject>
    <Content>My download speed likes to fluctuate between 500kbs and 2.0mbs, and i was wondering how to make my online games go faster i have a Nvidia 1 gb graphics card and the games i wanna play don&#039;t require anything close to that high. Even when i clean out my computer, optimized with a registry cleaner, and close all other programs there is still some lag. What is the reason for this ? Can someone help me?

Also i already called Time Warner they are no help at all they came here replaced our wireless router and said &quot; the readings im getting is good so bye&quot; so i need help plz

and i have already checked for port forwarding my games and for the one game i can find a way to port forward it doesn&#039;t make a difference in the lag and the games i cant find the ports for still lag just the same.

If it matters the Games are Combat Arms and Neo Steam that i have been playing lately and i cant find the ports for both of them.
What i mean by lag is that the character i use likes to skip and/or freeze for a few seconds every few seconds but i know that my computer can handle it because before i moved a month ago i had basic internet and the was no lag at all after i got my new graphics card
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-21 23:27:23</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269239243</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100321232723AAOefjT</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>fsY5bacLaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>chrisdunc15</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>1</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>my old computer is is very laging on my new computer it is very fast and my dads computer is little bit slow!@#4%^^&amp;*(()_-+=[{}]]|\:;&quot;&#039;&lt;,&gt;.?/</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>Ic1Uu1I0aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Ayancutepuppy</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269293606</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1270221843</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>What *precisely* do you mean by lag? People use the term &quot;lag&quot; to refer to everything from delayed response to game actions to low frame rates to rubberbanding. Without knowing what the problem is, there&#039;s no way to know what to suggest.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>ebuxHnScaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>JoelKatz</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-21 23:33:06</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269239586</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>my old computer is is very laging on my new computer it is very fast and my dads computer is little bit slow!@#4%^^&amp;*(()_-+=[{}]]|\:;&quot;&#039;&lt;,&gt;.?/</Content>
            <Reference>my computer</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>Ic1Uu1I0aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Ayancutepuppy</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-22 14:33:26</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269293606</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
        <Comment>
            <Content></Content>
            <UserId>CzI1Nogmaa</UserId>
            <UserNick></UserNick>
            <Date>2010-04-02 20:42:07</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269293606</Timestamp>
        </Comment>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws07.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:24:31 PDT 2010 -->
