<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100321220110AAPFCdM" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Is Freebieape.com a legit site?</Subject>
    <Content>I know that most sites are not legit when it comes to free stuff but i&#039;ve heard from some people I know that its real. Is it really?
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-21 22:01:10</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269234070</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100321220110AAPFCdM</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>1Wy6ce0xaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>tingling737</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I can&#039;t speak from experience but according to WOT (Web of Trust), it looks to be bogus. The WOT rating system is a really good tool for this type of issue. They have an add on for IE and Firefox.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>T6JiAnmeaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick></ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269234463</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269753300</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I can&#039;t speak from experience but according to WOT (Web of Trust), it looks to be bogus. The WOT rating system is a really good tool for this type of issue. They have an add on for IE and Firefox.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>T6JiAnmeaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Philip</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-21 22:07:43</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269234463</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I would say no but...

it Depends on what you mean by legit.

according to the fine print.

You have to sign up for 13 sposors and...

&quot;Please note Sponsor offers may require you to sample and/or purchase products of interest and/or take other actions such as applying for or obtaining a loan or extension of credit (including credit cards), transferring a balance, or similar steps.&quot;

You have to fill out several surveys

You could do all of these things and they could still not qualify for the gift... this would mean you still are subject to all the sponsors you signed up for and you can&#039;t take back the survey information you gave.

They seem pretty strict about the amount of time you have to do all this.

To summarize:

You have to sign up for 13 different promotions that may or may not require you to purchase things and even take out loans on interest bearing credit cards. You will have to give out personal information (not excluding credit and financial information). After you have done both of these things the site will decide if you qualify for the gift you are hoping to get.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>7UWis91Vaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Jacob G</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-21 22:18:48</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269235128</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws13.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:24:48 PDT 2010 -->
