<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100312203815AAVNbjw" type="Answered">
    <Subject>SO BORED! What should i do?</Subject>
    <Content>i cant get on tsl right now and im not allowed on myspace, facebook, etc.
im really bored and my friends are already asleep! so what can i do?? like online?? im to HYPER to go to sleep! plus its not even midnight.....
so give me sum sites please!!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-12 20:38:15</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268455095</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100312203815AAVNbjw</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>92L5HGEgaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>♫ muzic babii ♫</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://avatars.zenfs.com/users/1N7XqTipKAAECBmNnhBO4ZMcwKA==.medium.png</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>8</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I AM TWO!!!
I was on every website I could find but nothing helped so a I found an old DVD player and beat the crap out of it then tried to use it, all I heard was **sink** **sink** **sink**.
That helped me. You should try it.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>YtOpfxLfaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>alastickmn</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268455472</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268970881</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>this is a good webiste: www.funnyjunk.com</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>ichaqK7baa</UserId>
            <UserNick>JD</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 20:40:23</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268455223</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Try smalldeadanimals.com</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>Kb5s4h3paa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Procto-Boy</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 20:41:02</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268455262</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Bored.com, wherethehellismatt.com,improveverywhere.com,jack.zunino.net/knowjack.htm,www.newsandentertainment.com/zFbritney.html</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>hr4fyCLBaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Lucy Goosy</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 20:41:13</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268455273</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I AM TWO!!!
I was on every website I could find but nothing helped so a I found an old DVD player and beat the crap out of it then tried to use it, all I heard was **sink** **sink** **sink**.
That helped me. You should try it.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>YtOpfxLfaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>alastickmn</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 20:44:32</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268455472</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>you should let me invite you to lockerz.com

and start earning points for an ipod-touch or a mac book and al sorts of cool merchandise 

the site is free

in order for me to invite you i need you to give me your email and sign up
(its really quick give it a try you dont even have to use it but there are gifts)</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>Djnr1oY7aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>jakeramlow</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 20:44:37</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268455477</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>WWW.PLANETLIVECHAT.COM</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>iQmbeRXUaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Alley V</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 20:46:30</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268455590</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Bored? Listless? Help is at hand!
Pass away the pointless hours with our list of things to do when you&#039;re bored

Things you can do with absolutely nothing
Things you can do with very little
Things you can do with another person 

THINGS YOU CAN DO WITH ABSOLUTELY NOTHING

Blink wildly and then close your eyes really tight for an interesting light show
(Amusement Potential: 1-5 minutes)
See a variety of blobs, stars and flashes. Try to make out shapes and see if your subconscious is trying to send you a message (perhaps that funny shape is saying, &#039;send all your money to urban75.com&#039;?)

See how long you can hold a note
(Amusement Potential: 4-20 minutes)
Not that much fun, but it sure passes the time. Play with a friend, or try to beat your own personal best. Inhale deeply and then try and make a noise for as long as you can. Earn extra points for making your partner laugh or ending on an amusing note.

Try to not think about penguins
(Amusement Potential: 1-5 minutes)
This is especially hard, because by trying too much, you remember what you were trying to avoid thinking of. If you try too little, you end up thinking about penguins anyway.

Use your secret mind power
(Amusement Potential: 5-10 minutes)
Pick a passing by and try to use your mind power to command them do something, like drop their bag or knock into someone. The law of averages dictates that sooner or later one of your mind commands will come true, so you can convince yourself that you really have super human powers and waste even more time trying them out.

Pretend you&#039;re a robot
(Amusement Potential: 1-3 minutes)
Walk down the street with mechanical movements, adding &#039;zzzzzt&#039; sounds with each motion. Pretending to have a motor broken in, say, your left hand can add at least 30 seconds more entertainment. 

Scratch yourself
(Amusement Potential: 1-3 minutes)
Go ahead, scratch yourself now. Even if nothing itches, go ahead. Doesn&#039;t that feel pretty good?

Rate passers by
(Amusement Potential: 10-15 minutes)
Secretly award passers by marks out of ten as you go along, offering (unsaid) expert criticism over their clothing, hairstyle and footwear choices. 

Repeat the same word over and over until it loses its meaning
(Amusement Potential: 1-3 minutes)
Pick a random word out of a magazine and say it aloud to yourself until it becomes a meaningless set of noises.

Pinch yourself
(Amusement Potential: 1-3 minutes)
What is pain? Why is it unpleasant? There&#039;s nothing physical about it - it&#039;s all in your mind. Plus, after pinching yourself for awhile, boredom will seem nice next to being in pain.

Pretend to be a car
(Amusement Potential: 5-10 minutes)
Make appropriate revving noises in your head as you walk along and add a racing commentary as you pass strangers in the street. Use blinking eyes as indicators for extra authenticity. 

Make Star Trek door noises
(Amusement Potential: 1-2 minutes)
Stand by an electric door to a bank or something and make that silly &quot;Scccccccchwop&quot; sound heard whenever people popped on to the bridge to hang with Captain Kirk.

Look at something for awhile, shut eyes, study after image
(Amusement Potential: 2-5 minutes)
Another great time waster. It takes about 30 seconds of staring to create an after image, and the image is then viewable for about the same length of time. Fun to combine this one with pushing on your eyes.

Get yourself as nauseated as possible
(Amusement Potential: 5-10 minutes)
Best achieved by looking straight up and spinning around. Try to be so dizzy you can&#039;t even stand up. This is also entertaining due to the &quot;makes boredom seem a lot better&quot; effect (see &quot;Hurt Yourself&quot;). 

Invent a weird twitch
(Amusement Potential: 5-10 minutes)
Adopt a bizarre twitch (e.g. flicking your head irregularly, twitching with eye or busting out sporadic cough noises) and try it out when you go shopping. 

Make a low buzzing noise
(Amusement Potential: 15-30 minutes)
Hours of fun in libraries! Keeping a totally straight face and looking nonchalant, make a low pitch humming/buzzing noise and see who reacts. 



THINGS YOU CAN DO WITH VERY LITTLE

See what&#039;s in your neighbour&#039;s rubbish/trash
(Amusement Potential: 20-30 minutes)
You can learn a lot about people by what they throw out. You might uncover some dark secret about them. Plus, they might be throwing out something with value that still works, like a VCR or some porn mags.

Watch TV, repeat everything said in Italian accent
(Amusement Potential: 5-10 minutes)
Sort of entertaining. Include flamboyant shoulder shrugs for added impact, or go for a Marlon Brando set of grunts. 

Send spooky emails
(Amusement Potential: 15-60 minutes)
Look up someone&#039;s CV on the web, do some research on them via Google and then send them an email full of personal re</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>19YOG6jcaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>muffins r just ugly cupcakes</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 20:53:54</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268456034</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Www.1227.com</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>kluEl3Fvaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>BROFFY</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 22:56:35</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268463395</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws12.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:06:36 PDT 2010 -->
