<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100221132101AAq9xtE" type="Answered">
    <Subject>What should I do? Ebay question need help?</Subject>
    <Content>Hey I bought something for my dad for his birthday on ebay. I talked to the seller and planned on paying with a money order. It has been over a week since I won the item and I have sent him several emails and have not received a response. His birthday is approaching and I&#039;m not sure what to do. Is there a certain period in which the seller must give you the info to pay? I&#039;m thinking of ordering one from someone else but what would happen with the one I already ordered? Could it be canceled or something since he never contacted me? I am also beginning to wonder if it would even be safe to send him a money order since he has not even responded to me yet. What do you suggest I do?
I haven&#039;t gotten his information from him and haven&#039;t sent the money order since I don&#039;t know where to send it.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-21 13:21:01</Date>
    <Timestamp>1266787261</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100221132101AAq9xtE</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>9ze6bOMYaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>classyyetcrazy</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1EXbRr48zAAMDGcJ66BhyBg==.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Sorry but your on your own here. When buying from eBay you should ALWAYS use paypal because then you have a oney back guarantee for problems like this.Let&#039;s just hope you didnt pay TOO much.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>EzxJD1AHaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>TheDoctor</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1266787404</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267046456</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Sorry but your on your own here. When buying from eBay you should ALWAYS use paypal because then you have a oney back guarantee for problems like this.Let&#039;s just hope you didnt pay TOO much.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>1</Best>
            <UserId>EzxJD1AHaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>TheDoctor</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-21 13:23:24</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266787404</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I&#039;m not sure what the period is that the seller has to send you the item but I do know it is much longer than a week. I think it might be like 2 weeks at the least. you have a while to go before you should worry that your not gonna get it. If you can and haven&#039;t sent the money order yet I&#039;d highly suggest paying with pay pal so you can get your money back if he never sends it.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>dd23029b5081a567570f0b434bc00cacaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>jonny G</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-21 13:35:16</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266788116</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws05.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 02:33:46 PDT 2010 -->
