<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100320050738AAHP0aO" type="Answered">
    <Subject>How To Buy A Domain Name In The UK?</Subject>
    <Content>Hi. I want to buy a .com domain name for my UK based personal training company. Where is the best, legitimate place to purchase one? Many Thanks.
PLEASE don&#039;t suggest american websites, UK only please.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-20 05:07:38</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269086858</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100320050738AAHP0aO</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>c9xneNEtaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Matt K</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>4</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>http://www.domaincityhosting.com is US based but has servers in UK.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>Mhaun4IZaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Nate D</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269200195</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269606179</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>http://www.godaddy.com</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>nsiN6E3zaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Excessive MHz</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-20 05:08:09</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269086889</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>As you may know a domain name is just a name, not a real website. If you are going to create your website: 1- Buy a domain name. A domain name is a name you want to call your website (ex: www.yahoo.com). To get a domain name, you have to pay an annual fee to a registrar for the right to use that name. 2- Buy a web hosting service to provide your online space and enable you to get your website online at your purchased domain name.

If you want to start your website I recommend purchase your domain and hosting together. In this way it is possible to get your domain for free. Some hosting services offer this gift today.

As an experienced webmaster I recommend BH web hosting which I’m sure it would work for you and fulfill all your requirements. They have a really great offer for hosting &amp; I have used them for over 3 yrs now, and have never had a single problem with them. 

You can reach reviews about this web hosting provider and its latest DISCOUNT COUPONS at:


http://www.threehosts.com/reviews/1st

Only $3.95 /month (with discount coupon).


******IMPORTANT********
* This service was awarded the “Best Web Hosting OF The Year”.
* If you sign up for this service you will have $75 credits to advertise your website with the google &amp; yahoo search engines for free!
* You Can Register A Free Domain or Use Your Existing Domains. They Support All Domain Names.
****************************

Another useful link:
http://www.threehosts.com/build
There you can find a step-by-step guide to start your website.

Hope this helps.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>YsXKcAgbaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>David M</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-20 06:50:53</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269093053</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>http://www.domaincityhosting.com is US based but has servers in UK.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>Mhaun4IZaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Nate D</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-21 12:36:35</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269200195</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>In the much touted cyber democracy there are no actual boundaries , you can buy and domain name any where, try buying domain names from http://www.xnynz.com/ where u can procure domain names for less than 2$</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>OZMGfBntaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Radha Rodriguez</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-22 00:02:34</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269241354</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws07.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:32:18 PDT 2010 -->
