<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100331182601AAbOW66" type="Answered">
    <Subject>How does craigslist work?</Subject>
    <Content>I&#039;m thinking about putting my laptop for sale on craigslist because I think I can get more money there than ebay but craigslist just seems so sketchy. How exactly does it work? Is there an aunction? Do people email me bids and I accept whatever bid I want, can I just decide not to sell it once I&#039;v listed it?

Also, a lot of the items I&#039;v checked out say &quot;Cash only, won&#039;t ship&quot;. That means I have to give them my address so they can come to my house and pick it up? why do a lot of people want cash only? I use paypal all the time on ebay, is paypal not safe for craigslist?
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-31 18:26:01</Date>
    <Timestamp>1270085161</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100331182601AAbOW66</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>4fd48bxoaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>jmido8</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/49d8450ei18f7zul6re4/gGJ0NTA7dq.9EjHnrcM-/1/tn48.jpg?ciAAToMB2ce0RKv0</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Good answer above to clarify a little bit more as how to go about making your post better and safer. Take a photo of your laptop maybe a few that you will upload to craigslist also give a brief description of the specs of the laptop as well as the software that is included.

What I do next helps protect who I am DO NOT POST your phone number also use another email with a name like yours or a made up one when you set the deal through emails you could explain why you did this. 

Why others post &quot;Will Not Ship&quot; is the email from people Phishing and even down right fraud from other countries and the US is unbelievable.

When you go to sell it you meet in public that&#039;s where I have meet all my sales along the way and I have not been ripped yet and I have not ripped anyone else either. 

The name change was taught to me by a High School student when I was teaching at a local school. He suggested that when I selling or buying the name that is on the email is mine so they could find out where I live or who I am. Craigslist is safe for many reasons you get to email the person back and forth learning if they are legit or not and the biggest is I get to see the item I buying or if I am selling I get to see the defects.

I could list all that I bought let&#039;s just say almost half the items I bought are from there the other half from Amazon I love their return policy.

NOTE:
&quot;Cash only, won&#039;t ship&quot; when your selling an item most of the time your selling it locally yet some try to get you to ship them to you with &quot;I will buy your item at the price you ask and I am sending a courier over to pick it up and they will give you a Cashiers Check for the item please.

The check is as good as the ink and the paper as well I have known people who have bought an item and had it delivered as they where from a small town.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>QJD9v64Haa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>John Thom</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1270086259</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1270162650</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>no. basically craigslist is an &#039;ad site&#039;. u put ur ad on their and people respond. they can either e-mail u (they have an option for u 2 put ur e-mail private or not) or u can just leave ur phone # down in the ad. its kinda risky since ur revealing ur home address since ur selling it to the buyers if ur intending to sell it at ur house.</Content>
            <Reference>i use it</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>rZRhryjMaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Vball</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-31 18:29:46</Date>
            <Timestamp>1270085386</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Good answer above to clarify a little bit more as how to go about making your post better and safer. Take a photo of your laptop maybe a few that you will upload to craigslist also give a brief description of the specs of the laptop as well as the software that is included.

What I do next helps protect who I am DO NOT POST your phone number also use another email with a name like yours or a made up one when you set the deal through emails you could explain why you did this. 

Why others post &quot;Will Not Ship&quot; is the email from people Phishing and even down right fraud from other countries and the US is unbelievable.

When you go to sell it you meet in public that&#039;s where I have meet all my sales along the way and I have not been ripped yet and I have not ripped anyone else either. 

The name change was taught to me by a High School student when I was teaching at a local school. He suggested that when I selling or buying the name that is on the email is mine so they could find out where I live or who I am. Craigslist is safe for many reasons you get to email the person back and forth learning if they are legit or not and the biggest is I get to see the item I buying or if I am selling I get to see the defects.

I could list all that I bought let&#039;s just say almost half the items I bought are from there the other half from Amazon I love their return policy.

NOTE:
&quot;Cash only, won&#039;t ship&quot; when your selling an item most of the time your selling it locally yet some try to get you to ship them to you with &quot;I will buy your item at the price you ask and I am sending a courier over to pick it up and they will give you a Cashiers Check for the item please.

The check is as good as the ink and the paper as well I have known people who have bought an item and had it delivered as they where from a small town.</Content>
            <Reference>Experience:

I buy most of my bigger items, I also sell items online through them as well as barter that&#039;s another answer.

I went way to long............sorry</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>QJD9v64Haa</UserId>
            <UserNick>John Thom</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-31 18:44:19</Date>
            <Timestamp>1270086259</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws03.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:12:16 PDT 2010 -->
