<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100227120524AA6UXqy" type="Answered">
    <Subject>My aim messenger wont let me text but it did before... help me!?</Subject>
    <Content>okay, so I use aim messenger to text until I can get a new phone (mines broken).  I have been doing this all week, and I have used it in the past and its always worked fine.  Today I decided to give the numbers &quot;nicknames&quot; so I would know who I was texting. As soon as I did this, all the numbers went offline.  None of these numbers were connected to the persons user name, they were just numbers.  I thought maybe since I gave them nicknames it made them mess up, so I deleted the names and the contacts then tried to retext them.  This did not work.  I ended up making a whole new aim sn.  When I did this it again let me text them (yay) then I logged off and got on my previous sn to write down other contacts sn&#039;s.  When I logged back on, it would no longer let me send a text to that person.  I dont know why.  I am so confused on why it wont let me send it, it keeps saying they are offline, but they dont have an aim sn so that makes no sense.  It has not done this before and I dont know whats wrong, anyone else having the same problem?
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-27 12:05:24</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267301124</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100227120524AA6UXqy</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>6AM8FZ9paa</UserId>
    <UserNick>aat_06</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1dUabecD5AAED-2Fn-A6KiEH1LB8G.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>mines doing the same thing. not sure why though or how to fix it. its done this before. i think its a problem with all aim users in general. something aim is actually doing themselves. it will probably be fixed in a few hours or days. its stupid when it does this!</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>YaEr5nkEaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Misty.</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267306355</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267820755</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>mines doing the same thing. not sure why though or how to fix it. its done this before. i think its a problem with all aim users in general. something aim is actually doing themselves. it will probably be fixed in a few hours or days. its stupid when it does this!</Content>
            <Reference>myself.</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>YaEr5nkEaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Misty.</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-27 13:32:35</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267306355</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws07.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:43:47 PDT 2010 -->
