<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100317101530AA9bMCv" type="Answered">
    <Subject>lockerz redemption question?</Subject>
    <Content>idk wut the redemtion rules r, im not talkin for a month im talkin the rules mainly...wut r they?
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-17 10:15:30</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268846130</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100317101530AA9bMCv</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>SQp2cKnWaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>sophie_issa</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1In0e8vmvAAADBAOclCBVBtik3bWrtQ==.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>1</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>what the fuck are you on about?  lockerz is shit.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>rrXjSKiOaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Stanley</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268846219</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269148165</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>what the fuck are you on about?  lockerz is shit.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>rrXjSKiOaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Stanley</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 10:16:59</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268846219</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>The first rule is : There are no rules.

There has been a passing movement amongst the coalition of locker stuffers out there ; Ellison(2008) stated that in the Western European Board Meeting of Locker Crimes that most kids end up glamorizing their incident and talk about it a lot (Lockerz Magazine, p. 392). The outcome of this has been numerous tattoos spiting their hurter.

You could try attending some group sessions on locker redemption. I&#039;ve been to one meeting where the victims plotted revenge and successfully knocked off the perfect plan. We&#039;ll just say the bully&#039;s name was Jimmy and the victim, someone 50 pounds less and 3 years younger, really steamed the emotions of his fellow members in the club. They united and formed a for-profit organization to revenge people. Their first job was locking up Jimmy. They strategized for hours and came up with their solution at 530pm. They found Jimmy smoking in the parking lot. Jimmy swallowed his cigarette when they saw 3 small boyz coming up to him with cruel intentions. The dragged Jimmy into the school and locked him in the locker overnightz. You should have been there, it got ugly. 

There&#039;s been some abuses of the &#039;revenge&#039; system where the group was hired by liars. People who hadn&#039;t been locked in a locker lied and said they were, and innocent people were locked up (it aint punny). Lesson is, let the law take care of the lawkerz, and you can focus on just making your way through it with the support of other clownz with frownz.

Peace dawg.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>Q84sTMR4aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Jade</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 10:24:22</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268846662</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>http://bit.ly/aFlQMe</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>JlLVAIDhaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Ty</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-17 13:32:02</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268857922</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
        <Comment>
            <Content></Content>
            <UserId>Q84sTMR4aa</UserId>
            <UserNick></UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-22 21:40:05</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268857922</Timestamp>
        </Comment>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws01.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:44:33 PDT 2010 -->
