<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100223124544AAwaONB" type="Answered">
    <Subject>SKYPE!!!!?!??? please help me!?</Subject>
    <Content>Ok, so I finally made a skype account &#039;cause my friend told me to. And I&#039;m wondering, WHAT IS SKYPE? Like what&#039;s its purpose and what can you do on it? Is it like calling or instant messaging or video chat? WHAT IS IT? And it&#039;s completely FREE, right? My parents would kill me if they get a bill!! So, I won&#039;t get charged for instant messaging , calling or v-chatting with someone? Another thing, my friend lives in France and I live in California, USA. Does international calls or whatever, cost? Help me and tell me what I should know! Pleeeease! Thanks so much! Answer my questions and tell me how it works and all that. I&#039;d soooo appreciate it. Much love! xoxo
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-23 12:45:44</Date>
    <Timestamp>1266957944</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100223124544AAwaONB</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>FxixVUSUaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>pinktink011</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1_exbbdn6AAED9IF3zBZVhkF7LA==.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>skype everything is free
chat, calls all over the world, video conversations
all free
alot people use it
dont buy skype credit u dont have to</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>e3kZkbn5aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>watermelon</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1266958134</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268293924</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>skype everything is free
chat, calls all over the world, video conversations
all free
alot people use it
dont buy skype credit u dont have to</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>e3kZkbn5aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Watermelon</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-23 12:48:54</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266958134</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>A Skype is part of the mainframe of the internet, controlled by Sky Net (hence the SKYpe). Yes, they do charge you, eleven internets to be exact. You gain internets by turning in humans to Sky Net and helping build Terminators (there are the terminals that transmit your message). 
France is a long ways, so lets do the math. State to state talk is 11 internets. Multiplied by fifty states and you have 550 internets. Then add foreign bills, charges, and tip (for good service) and that it around 800 or so internets. No too bad, I pay a thousand internets for access to the Sky Net overlord control mainframe.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>pqeaHWLJaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Dude D</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-23 12:50:23</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266958223</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>skype you can call your friends on others computers you ONLY have to pay if you choose to purchase a subsciption or credit (that you use to call landline phones) there are no hidden charges and its only a few bucks if your interested</Content>
            <Reference>skype user</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>ZllkWRIOaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Mr. HotShot</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-23 13:00:57</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266958857</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws15.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 02:19:46 PDT 2010 -->
