<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100315134754AA0BoAg" type="Answered">
    <Subject>EBAY HELP! inexperienced users of ebay...?</Subject>
    <Content>So I have never used ebay... and my sister made an account and bid on a purse. she didnt know bidding was final and that once you bid you have to pay if you have won.... she thought that you would be contacted as the winner and if you win you can choose to pay or it will go to the second highest bidder! so she doesnt have the money because my parents wont let her buy it anymore. is there a way to cancel it? if she doesn&#039;t pay will anything happen to her? will we have a bill sent to us? or anything? or will the seller just drop it and try selling it again?
yeahh i never use ebay so i dont care if it will look bad... we are deleting the account because of this problem.. but it cant be deleted for 180 days.. i was just nervous that something would happen! my sister did contact the seller but the seller hasnt responded... but it said that she couldnt pay for the item and didnt understand what happened when bidding on ebay! so hopefully the seller will just drop it and not do anything! thanks!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-15 13:47:54</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268686074</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100315134754AA0BoAg</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>AA10129361</UserId>
    <UserNick>xxLiVEsmileLAUGHxx</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://avatars.zenfs.com/users/11PJNGLHWAAEDXaObAB4PtPgA.medium.png</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>you will get no bill but she will get negative mark on her ebay status and may not be able to buy anything else there</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>esYTfoYraa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>topdn</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268686493</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269205673</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>you will get no bill but she will get negative mark on her ebay status and may not be able to buy anything else there</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>esYTfoYraa</UserId>
            <UserNick>topdn</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-15 13:54:53</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268686493</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Well first contact the person you bought it from go to &#039;ask seller question&#039; and ask if you can cancel your transaction. If he says no then it will just look bad on your account. no you can not get in trouble its no big deal calm down. They will try to sell it again.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>g8vxxcQoaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>nicole w</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-15 13:55:26</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268686526</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws15.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:53:32 PDT 2010 -->
