<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100327183113AA68IJy" type="Answered">
    <Subject>How can I protect a certain site that I go on from getting a virus again?</Subject>
    <Content>The site I go on to download my music is www.mp3raid.com, and it has free music on it so of course its illegal but everyone downloads illegal music so whatever.  Haha anywayssss I would always go on that site to download all my music and one day I got a virus and I had no idea where i got that virus from. I didn&#039;t know how to check where I got the virus from. So that virus drove me absolutely crazyyyyyy. So my mom took it to this guy she knew at best buy and he took off the virus from my computer for free. And he said that i got the virus from the website i would go on to download my music (www.mp3raid.com). So my mom told me not to go on the website again so that I don&#039;t get a virus, and I DEFINETLY dont want a virus again. But the problem is, theres no other website out there like mp3raid.com. All the other websites you have to pay money for and I can&#039;t do that cuz my parents wont let me. So my question is, Is there any way that I can protect that music website from giving me another virus??
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-27 18:31:13</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269739873</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100327183113AA68IJy</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>dciIS41aaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>ღ☻♥$om3 R@N:D0m G!RL♥☻ღ</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/4b0e21afi4f6zul8sp1/uUPo_psgeqjC_I.SmfiMZzeh92Pd6FFj/11/tn48.jpg?ciAAToMBFJgf8PMO</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Although what you are doing is illegal, I suggest you get a Virus Scanner like Anti-Virus Guard or Avira. Every download you do, Scan with one of those programs before opening. If you download often, Scan your computer everyday.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>KrJMhAwqaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Sombix</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269742694</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269829074</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Although what you are doing is illegal, I suggest you get a Virus Scanner like Anti-Virus Guard or Avira. Every download you do, Scan with one of those programs before opening. If you download often, Scan your computer everyday.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>KrJMhAwqaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Sombix</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-27 19:18:14</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269742694</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws03.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:21:34 PDT 2010 -->
