<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100306145914AAzN5cX" type="Answered">
    <Subject>help with lockerz?  ptz needed?</Subject>
    <Content>I have been a member of lockerz for about a month and i have 632ptz.
Im trying to get a macbook pro 13 in. by July (my b-day) so my parents won&#039;t have to buy me a laptop.
I only wanted to know if lockerz REALLY works or if  I&#039;m wasting my time.


also if u want an invite SEND ME AN EMAIL!! don&#039;t leave any info here.



Does lockerz really work or should i Justin quit?
thnx
I meant should i JUST quit, at the end.

i was thinking about justin bieber lol
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-06 14:59:14</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267916354</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100306145914AAzN5cX</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>1mvvXBqOaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>JayJu93</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>How did you get 632 ptz in a month? I watched every vid and im VIP and i have 247 in a month.. thats the max you get. It works search on youtube &quot;Lockerz unboxing&quot;</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>b5XmSMu7aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Justin</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268098438</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268435798</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>It’s a scam. I was a member of lockerz for 3 months and never got a thing. I ordered an ipod nano and it NEVER came. I called the company and asked them to give me a refund but they would not do it. Don&#039;t trust them it’s a scam! I found points2shop and its way better.

Points2shop is by far the best site for earning free cash/prizes. I&#039;ve been a member of all the get free stuff websites: Prizerebel, Swagbucks, Lockerz, Rewards1, and cashcrate. They were all really hard to earn points on. It was very time consuming. And I never got anything from those sites.

If I were you I&#039;d go to points2shop. You can earn points so easily on points2shop by completing offers, surveys, playing games, or simply by clicking on links! It’s that easy! I just received an ipod nano from points2shop in the mail last month. You get all your prizes directly off amazon.com, which makes shopping for prizes a lot easier because amazon has every item you could possibly want. 

Points2shop is best, fastest, and easiest site for getting free stuff. Best of all Points2shop is 100% free.If you need to know more information you can check their forums where members post the things that they have received for earning points on the points2shop website below.

The only way to get 250 free bonus points is by going to the link below and signing up.

http://www.points2shop.com/?ref=salibu</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>x8xgpyLQaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>thom</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-07 10:25:25</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267986325</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>How did you get 632 ptz in a month? I watched every vid and im VIP and i have 247 in a month.. thats the max you get. It works search on youtube &quot;Lockerz unboxing&quot;</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>b5XmSMu7aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Justin</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 17:33:58</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268098438</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws04.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:45:45 PDT 2010 -->
