<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100312005339AA1VEOc" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Which is your favourite social networking site and why you like it most?</Subject>
    <Content>
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-12 00:53:39</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268384019</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100312005339AA1VEOc</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>WROdHuuKaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Bittu</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/4b7bbc75i1664zul7sp1/J9sdjFU1c6cGKYEF2Gv9RcB0jzBSP_ql/5/tn48.jpg?ciAAToMB4xVq46Q5</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>11</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>My popular Social Networking Sites are Orkut And Facebook. 
Because after using this Sites I found many Old friends by this Sites. Facebook is very Fast than Orkut. It suggests you to Add some of friends which you might be knowing them. 
Orkut also introduced this Facility this year.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>UgcAb9TVaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>ks</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268384249</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268467756</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Orkut</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>LuL87JrQaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Immu</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 00:54:33</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268384073</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>My favourite is Facebook by far :) I like it because its easy to use... Its set out very good... And Aot of people use it... And i mean ALOT! :) hope i Helped :)</Content>
            <Reference>Me, Myself and I</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>hRgMiXTYaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Hi</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 00:55:41</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268384141</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Orkut..because all my friends are  there :) :)</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>ec3bc41d58ce1c2991e8b3b09e084c9caa</UserId>
            <UserNick>coolguy</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 00:56:28</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268384188</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>My popular Social Networking Sites are Orkut And Facebook. 
Because after using this Sites I found many Old friends by this Sites. Facebook is very Fast than Orkut. It suggests you to Add some of friends which you might be knowing them. 
Orkut also introduced this Facility this year.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>4</Best>
            <UserId>UgcAb9TVaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>ks</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 00:57:29</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268384249</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I like Facebook, because I can play Farmville and Island Paradise and take lots of stupid quizzes.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>26oBnkMXaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>delicioussoul</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 00:58:19</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268384299</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE MYSPACE</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>E60B78rLaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>| ✈ ησαн |</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 01:27:28</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268386048</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>First, Facebook, and second, Windows Live.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>s641dmqSaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>xdmwe</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 03:00:49</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268391649</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Orcut is the best for friends
linkedin is good for professional network</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>KDnalwyWaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Shilpa Singh</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 05:30:18</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268400618</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>orkut</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>poXM1WvLaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Kumar</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 09:33:13</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268415193</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Scallyroo.com because it is exclusively for teens and there are no creepers trolling on it. Plus it has a bunch of really neat apps</Content>
            <Reference>I am a member 6 social networks and Scallyroo is the best (http://www.scallyroo.com)</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>1gR7jBvPaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Diana R NYC</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 13:00:36</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268427636</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>i only ever use Fubar now.there is so much more to do there
http://www.fubar.com/mafia/join.php?acceptinv=671</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>HCEkcD9oaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Mental</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-12 16:40:32</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268440832</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws10.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:11:03 PDT 2010 -->
