<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100320071422AAEVGVK" type="Answered">
    <Subject>For WebTV or MSNTV2, will it work on a digital converter box, or only cable?</Subject>
    <Content>If you have your own internet provider like cable internet does your internet provider bill get reduced at $10 a month.  I&#039;m paying $50 dollars a month for cable internet and is too much $$money. I know it can use dial-up, but dial-up is too slow. Right now have cable but was thinking of disconnecting the services getting a digital antenna and converter box  Would WebTV or MSNTV2 work with the converter box or should I keep the cable services for the internet?. I&#039;m thinking of using a digital antenna to watch my TV channels. This TV is the new HDTV however, so it doesn&#039;t need a digital converter box. Also can it be use on several TV sets or just one box per TV?  Also which is better MSNTV2 or Sony WebTV?

    
Additional Details
Ifyou provide your own internet service like cable internet which I was paying $50 a month. Would I have to still pay $50 dollars a month or just $10 a month? Is the the $10 a month seperate or included? Soit would come out to a total of $60 a month to use the internet or webtv or just $10 a month?

54 seconds ago
Do I have to have cable tv services or will it work on free antenna and converter box.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-20 07:14:22</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269094462</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100320071422AAEVGVK</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>Ye7xL8Vraa</UserId>
    <UserNick>lolitagirl</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1KMnKTF_HAAECnIJ3dJOXBQ==.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Microsoft’s $10 monthly charge for MSNTV2 is in addition to your internet service provider (ISP).

Fifty dollars is too much for broadband. MSNTV2 will also work with DSL broadband available from land line phone companies for as little as $15 monthly. 

Wireless phone companies (i.e. Verizon) offer broadband via a ‘dongle’ for about $40 monthly. This is not MSNTV2 compatible without the addition of computer and router.

I am unaware of any Internet Service Provider available via digital UHF antennae used for HDTV. 

Sony’s WebTV is the best of the original dialup Web TVs. RCA’s MSNTV2 is compatible with broadband and much, much quicker. 

If you think of any additional questions feel free to contact me.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>AA10030685</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>WebtvDan</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269123595</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269614026</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Microsoft’s $10 monthly charge for MSNTV2 is in addition to your internet service provider (ISP).

Fifty dollars is too much for broadband. MSNTV2 will also work with DSL broadband available from land line phone companies for as little as $15 monthly. 

Wireless phone companies (i.e. Verizon) offer broadband via a ‘dongle’ for about $40 monthly. This is not MSNTV2 compatible without the addition of computer and router.

I am unaware of any Internet Service Provider available via digital UHF antennae used for HDTV. 

Sony’s WebTV is the best of the original dialup Web TVs. RCA’s MSNTV2 is compatible with broadband and much, much quicker. 

If you think of any additional questions feel free to contact me.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>AA10030685</UserId>
            <UserNick>WebtvDan</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-20 15:19:55</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269123595</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws09.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:31:52 PDT 2010 -->
