<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100310171958AArYuoh" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Lockers SHUT DOWN FOR GOOD?</Subject>
    <Content>After doing countless research i found out that Lockerz is actually a scam and i got 592 PTZ for nothing I want to report this internet site for fraud for not giving away no real prizes and have it SHUT DOWN does anyone know where i can report that fake crap you call Lockerz(WTF Is with that name anyway?) Can I contact the FBI,The government,God? Just to get this site off the internet(I don&#039;t want to resort to hacking)
Oh forgot to add lockerz pays people to say its not a scam and make videos of them unboxing prizes What a load of bull...
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-10 17:19:58</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268270398</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100310171958AArYuoh</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>52pUUUzcaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Pspraider</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>6</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Calm down. Where did you get your info. It might not be accurate. Lockerz is most probably not a scam. I know friends that got stuff off of it. It could just be that Lockerz is currently out of stock. Sometimes it crashes. And why would Lockerz be a scam. The more people on the site, the more advertisers want to advertise there. And they pay Thousands of dollars to pay for all of the prizes. And more. I think you are just panicking. And also, The last statement, I quote, &quot; Just to get this site off the internet(I don&#039;t want to resort to hacking)&quot; Could be used as a statement to send you to court. It legally qualifies as a threat. So, be careful with your word statement later.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>z5Apu5Uuaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>AngelicSight</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268270890</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268430624</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>BBB might do something</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>0LLpfL8Waa</UserId>
            <UserNick>The Mackinator</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-10 17:23:13</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268270593</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>It took you that long to figure out Lockerz is a scam?</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>kxsvjGmTaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>John C</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-10 17:23:41</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268270621</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I hate scams as much as you do. If you want a legitimate site to make money online try triond. It is free and easy to use. This is how I make around 3 dollars a day , writing only 2 recipes a day.

http://webupon.com/money-making/how-to-make-money-online-the-triond-way/</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>dZ6tcfULaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Bran Flakes</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-10 17:24:55</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268270695</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Calm down. Where did you get your info. It might not be accurate. Lockerz is most probably not a scam. I know friends that got stuff off of it. It could just be that Lockerz is currently out of stock. Sometimes it crashes. And why would Lockerz be a scam. The more people on the site, the more advertisers want to advertise there. And they pay Thousands of dollars to pay for all of the prizes. And more. I think you are just panicking. And also, The last statement, I quote, &quot; Just to get this site off the internet(I don&#039;t want to resort to hacking)&quot; Could be used as a statement to send you to court. It legally qualifies as a threat. So, be careful with your word statement later.</Content>
            <Reference>My head.</Reference>
            <Best>3</Best>
            <UserId>z5Apu5Uuaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>AngelicSight</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-10 17:28:10</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268270890</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Calm down. It&#039;s not a scam. Advertisers fund Lockerz, alright? Sometimes they get out of stock and a few people don&#039;t get their prizes. Only around 1%, and if you contact them, you can report the problem and get your prize. And seriously, contacting the FBI, the government, or God? That&#039;s way too high for this kind of stuff. Not everything you read is true. I could say that hippos can fly and repost it a hundred times, but that doesn&#039;t make it true. Also, HACKING IS ILLEGAL, dumbass. You could get arrested for threatening to hack a site.</Content>
            <Reference>Common sense</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>YDoUcocqaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Reni</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-10 18:48:16</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268275696</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Dude chill out, You are spending you life on this website to get a 50 dollar game. Oh i got a better idea may be get a job and then buy your little game it only takes 2 weak to get 50 dollars. better that 3 years. You wanna go through court just because you didnt get your little game. 

but for lockerz, it is a real website, sometimes u do get your prize sometimes you dont. most of the time its out of stock.....so calm your self and i wish i contact god to.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>fDsn3IrSaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Anthony</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-10 20:08:03</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268280483</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws04.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:16:40 PDT 2010 -->
