<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100304052005AA4Hp34" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Make money online without much skill (survey etc is fine)?</Subject>
    <Content>I searched make money online sites but there are too many sites and it seems fake. I don&#039;t know which one is actually true and really works. So is there anyone who is using money making websites? (sites that u don&#039;t have to pay or give ur credit card info etc) I heard that there is survey site that pays you. If anyone know real site please tell me :)
Thank you all ^^ I really appreciate it. I tried every site you suggested but there is one big problem &gt;_&lt; I&#039;m from Japan. I guess there is no online site for international... That&#039;s kinda sucks kkk :P But I&#039;m sure your answers will be useful for others :) 
If you know international site then pls let me know!! ^^
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-04 05:20:05</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267708805</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100304052005AA4Hp34</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>YS5rryc2aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>starmoon</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1IfESAf4hAAEBJmN2jBNVVvHgnlsE.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>6</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>You could try network marketing. It allows you to work around your schedule, kids, school, etc.

Find something that peaks your interest. Perhaps make-up, clothing, accessories, shoes, health products, cleaning products, baskets, etc.

Just find something that you can get excited about and then go for it.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>oUSQYJfVaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>everett</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267743781</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268228089</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Scam</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>3kmglEcZaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Danny</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 05:22:23</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267708943</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>The simple answer, that you don&#039;t want to hear, is that they are all scams.

There are a couple, and I mean only 1 or 2, &quot;secret shopper&quot; programs that are legit, although it requires you to check out particular stores, rate dozens of different things you observe, send in documentation, etc. and you get paid $10 to $20 per &quot;job&quot; that will likely take you an hour or two to complete.  Payment takes 4 to 8 weeks.  I don&#039;t remember the name of it, but they do NOT ask for *any* kind of financial information, no payment up-front etc...

Some survey sites like harris pol online are also legit, but they send you 1 or 2 surveys a week and you get &quot;points&quot; that you can trade for items like cordless phones, a magazine subscritpion etc.  Expect about a year to get enough points for a $40 cordless phone... 

You simply are not going to find a legitimate &quot;make real money&quot; offer on the internet.  If it came in through email, it is *guaranteed* to be a scam.  If it was a pop-up on a web site, it&#039;s also 100% scam.  If it came up in a search, but wasn&#039;t a pop-up, it&#039;s 99.99% likely to be a scam.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>pwk5xyLyaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Brian F</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 05:27:55</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267709275</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>you can try &quot;get paid to&quot; sites, in resources is one I use and I earn $20/month only from referrals</Content>
            <Reference>http://buxp.info</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>BpqE8PdVaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Pan</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 05:44:41</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267710281</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>You could try network marketing. It allows you to work around your schedule, kids, school, etc.

Find something that peaks your interest. Perhaps make-up, clothing, accessories, shoes, health products, cleaning products, baskets, etc.

Just find something that you can get excited about and then go for it.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>oUSQYJfVaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>everett</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 15:03:01</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267743781</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Hey i am 13 and make HUNDREDS of this method!
http://www.envirofile.org/download/14044
Seriously give it a go!</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.envirofile.org/download/14044</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>eVzY39fLaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Sachin</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 01:32:47</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267867967</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I was doing hard work of finding home based/ online jobs. Luckily I found this website:
http://workathome-opportunities.info They gave me list of top companies. I clicked and find many jobs. Did one job and received my pay yesterday. Best place for home based jobs.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>gkpucyxvaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>zahid</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 02:21:31</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267870891</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws02.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:12:14 PDT 2010 -->
