<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100330020435AAiWAdM" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Why do all the scams come from Nigeria?</Subject>
    <Content>i mean there are other poor countries around the world that could do this. so why is nigeria behind just about al of them, is the government in on it??
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-30 02:04:35</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269939875</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100330020435AAiWAdM</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>o6xzYw8uaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>ßѾßƧ</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/4b988ad6i514zws107sp2/Saizsvkpf6WmZLBIwz2uCz4k/1/tn48.jpeg?ciAAToMBboK0F5i6</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>4</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>No, but it&#039;s the law there. In Nigeria you do not become a man at 21. You become a man when you successfully scam an American.
So Nigerians have to scam in order to be allowed to vote and to drink</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>TUSlGuPOaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Redundant</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269940014</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1270035106</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>They say they are from Nigeria but some are not
Besides I&#039;ve had some from other places too</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>bYZsW1zAaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Lola</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-30 02:05:26</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269939926</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>No, but it&#039;s the law there. In Nigeria you do not become a man at 21. You become a man when you successfully scam an American.
So Nigerians have to scam in order to be allowed to vote and to drink</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>TUSlGuPOaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Luci</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-30 02:06:54</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269940014</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>These are not scams, there is a legitimate reason as it is because Nigeria has so many millionaires that have recently passed away and their dying wish was to give away their entire wealth to a total stranger living in a foreign country. Now please will you give me your bank account and sort code details so I can send you some money for your intelligent question?</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>JERCCG54aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Jason</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-30 02:08:08</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269940088</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>a large number of the scams come from nigeria but most dont. the reason is because due to lack of  skilled jobs educated nigerian brothers like my self use the scams and hacking skills they possess and rip people off (personally i dont, i live in Britain) . other scammers use nigerian names and locations because they seem to work with scams. personally i dont understand how people fall for this ridiculous scams are people really that STUPID. also nigeria, has the highest population in africa and one of the highest in the world. so by population, poverty and probability, a large number silly scams will come from nigeria. 

now having said this i would like to add that as the prince of nigeria i would really be grateful for a small donation in order to unlock my bank account thank u.

http://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20100330084536AAWdViT&amp;r=w</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>SYiKUNEhaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Mace W</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-30 07:19:17</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269958757</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws14.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:14:46 PDT 2010 -->
