<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100221172126AA8aR2o" type="Answered">
    <Subject>What should I do? Ebay question need help?</Subject>
    <Content>Hey I bought something for my dad for his birthday on ebay. I talked to the seller and planned on paying with a money order. It has been over a week since I won the item and I have sent him several emails and have not received a response. His birthday is approaching and I&#039;m not sure what to do. Is there a certain period in which the seller must give you the info to pay? I&#039;m thinking of ordering one from someone else but what would happen with the one I already ordered? Could it be canceled or something since he never contacted me? I am also beginning to wonder if it would even be safe to send him a money order since he has not even responded to me yet. What do you suggest I do?
I haven&#039;t gotten his information from him and haven&#039;t sent the money order since I don&#039;t know where to send it.
Also, I don&#039;t have a paypal account
Yeah I am 20

We agreed before I bid that I could pay with a money order and now he is not responding to my emails telling me where to send it. Isn&#039;t there a certain time period that he has to tell me were to send it?
also I know that he is active as he keeps listing new items yet he doesn&#039;t answer my messages
to harley- that is not an option I just tried
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-21 17:21:26</Date>
    <Timestamp>1266801686</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100221172126AA8aR2o</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>9ze6bOMYaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>classyyetcrazy</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1EXbRr48zAAMDGcJ66BhyBg==.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>go to the auction page , sign in and click &quot;pay now&quot; if the option to pay by money order is there all the seller&#039;s details for postage will also be there</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>2Bxy8GO6aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Harley Drive</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1266802577</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267046486</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>he can have you in breach for not paying
you should have had a paypal account and then you would have been able to pay for it

but how old are you are you of legal age to buy from ebay anyway</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>JuJTnZSDaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Dennis PC Repairs</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-21 17:26:39</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266801999</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>go to the auction page , sign in and click &quot;pay now&quot; if the option to pay by money order is there all the seller&#039;s details for postage will also be there</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>3</Best>
            <UserId>2Bxy8GO6aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Harley Drive</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-21 17:36:17</Date>
            <Timestamp>1266802577</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws08.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 02:32:29 PDT 2010 -->
