<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100306144348AAeXAN1" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Does my computer have a virus ?</Subject>
    <Content>For the past few months, everytime I&#039;ve gotten on Myspace, this fake Antivirus website would pop up, saying it was searching my computer for viruses and that I&#039;ve been infected. I ignored it because I knew it was fake and I immediately closed it out. But starting today, something strange has started popping up. I got on my computer earlier today, and some website having to do with wq32 kept popping up, and just recently when I was on Myspace editing my page, this popup box kept popping up. It said &quot;Are You Human?&#039; &amp;+ had two choices, &quot;OK&quot;, or &quot;Cancel&quot; I kept clicking OK, and it kept popping up no matter how many times I pressed it. Eventually it took me to this website called http://podmena.us and required that I type in some type of login information. I&#039;m getting extremely worried now, because I had another computer crash due to viruses and I really don&#039;t want to lose everything again. I do have McAfee Virus protection, but it has expired and my computer is not fully protected. Can somebody please let me know what might be wrong and what I can do to fix it ? Thank you !
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-06 14:43:48</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267915428</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100306144348AAeXAN1</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>yZ8KEk8Laa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Orangutan</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>antivirus tips and antivirus download:
http://merakit-komputer.com
http://merakit-komputer.com</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>rlrruu5Iaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Google</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267975412</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267976168</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>yes it has a virus . honestLy i donno how can we fix the probLem.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>kAYCUmk5aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>♀ m!$s $eXTEEN ♀</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 14:51:50</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267915910</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Sounds to me like the protection you had on was a trial version.The answer is updating and keeping an eye on the web based pages you go to. Another thing is you just may be getting the minor affects of &quot;Mal-ware&quot; or the other viruses that come with bad luck. 
 Here is the download link to the Malwarebytes, it may help rid the problematic occurrences

http://download.cnet.com/3001-8022_4-10804572.html?spi=e2fb8ed2384f7a34f6d2bd10e0da4d89

Another thing is, You may want to back up your PC up with an external hard drive incase the problem gets worse and formating is the only option.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>FE1HfjISaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Da Blanco</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 14:56:53</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267916213</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>antivirus tips and antivirus download:
http://merakit-komputer.com
http://merakit-komputer.com</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>rlrruu5Iaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Google</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-07 07:23:32</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267975412</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws04.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:45:54 PDT 2010 -->
