<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100304081048AAiQEoW" type="Answered">
    <Subject>How can I make more money as a webcam girl?</Subject>
    <Content>I think I&#039;m pretty my customers tell me I&#039;m pretty. One of the male models on the site visits my room sometimes and he said I&#039;m in the top percent of better looking girls on the site. I saw the other girls. Many are average looking. Alot of the girls don&#039;t even look like their pics when you go to their room. I look like my pics. Some aren&#039;t even fit but I guess they have other assets I don&#039;t have.

I have medium boobs and a medium butt. I am proportionate and in above average shape. I could tone up a bit more. Would that make a huge difference?
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-04 08:10:48</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267719048</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100304081048AAiQEoW</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>ctJc4jotaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Lovely Latina</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/q/users/1FgKHgEu4AAEDQqGa1E6C-rMB.medium.jpg</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>7</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>In my opinion it will make a huge difference if you tone up. The sexier you are in my opinion the more money you will make.

I see female cam models who are body builders with great bodies and there are always in private chats making money.

So in my opinion yes it would make a huge difference if you tone up.

You may also find this site interesting</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>3kBaY1Fwaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Jason</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267755560</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269099731</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>It&#039;s all a numbers game. Consider investing money in an advertising campaign, possibly using traditional (print) media. Viral marketing can be effective if it&#039;s clever. If you have some money to spare, a great Superbowl advertisement will get everyone talking about your business.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>ADA8eNKMaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Joel</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 08:14:01</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267719241</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>The company you work for make a huge difference.  Why not set up your own site where it is just you &quot;performing&quot; and have your own .com website.   I am a web designer and I could build you a professional site for very very cheap</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>RGojRInzaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>cs.c0sa</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 08:14:10</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267719250</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>go for it? will not know till you start doing it.make sure you are on a safe web-site? best of luck to you.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>GZXZl131aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>mommy</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 08:19:27</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267719567</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Like the song says, &quot;Take off all your clothes&quot;!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>YKrXugjTaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>David</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 08:54:59</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267721699</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>can you send me a link to your area</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>OP0WnHYZaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>bbl</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 12:53:01</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267735981</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>In my opinion it will make a huge difference if you tone up. The sexier you are in my opinion the more money you will make.

I see female cam models who are body builders with great bodies and there are always in private chats making money.

So in my opinion yes it would make a huge difference if you tone up.

You may also find this site interesting</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.internetmodeling.com/1278/application.htm</Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>3kBaY1Fwaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Jason</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-04 18:19:20</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267755560</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>It&#039;s not all about looks. It&#039;s about personality too. You have to get those guys so worked up that they are going to spend money on a private chat. The site you are on has a lot to do with it too. I&#039;ve seen sites out there that have a high per minute rate, but don&#039;t have a lot of traffic and leave their models to &quot;sink or swim&quot;. I work for the site Jason linked to. Their per minute rate is less than a lot of others, but the money ends up being better because 1. they put your cam on over 1000 sites that get more traffic in a day than some sites get in a month, 2. they have no chargebacks, 3. They train and support models to help them be more successful.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>PC6veWMiaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>web_cam_recruiter</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 22:24:15</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267943055</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws14.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:11:33 PDT 2010 -->
