<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100226155010AAKndVK" type="Answered">
    <Subject>My AIM is telling me I have the wrong password or user name, but when I go to change it it&#039;s wrong?</Subject>
    <Content>Today, I tried to sign on to AIM and it said that my password or username was incorrect. The thing is; I have it set to remember me AND my password. So I refreshed and tried to sign in again. It didn&#039;t work. After this, I clicked &quot;Forgot Password?&quot; so that I could change it. When I got to the page that came up, my screen name was already entered into the box, and I just had to enter the letters to the captcha thing or whatever... I am ONE HUNDRED percent sure that the screen name was right. Also; I am 100% sure that the text I entered to &#039;prove that I am human&#039; was correct. After hitting enter, I got an error message on the page. &quot;Not able to process your request. Please try again.&quot; So I tried again. And again, and again. Never worked. For some reason, I&#039;m thinking someone hacked into my account, but that still wouldn&#039;t change my user name, would it? So I&#039;m trying to figure out what happened and how I can get my AIM properly working. Please help, and thanks!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-26 15:50:10</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267228210</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100226155010AAKndVK</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>e2IM94g0aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>srompo1821</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/4b6869c3i24a7zul8re4/i5PEO_Uiaan78f7Z8UQVCyaV/1/tn48.jpg?ciAAToMBoOnrBBVs</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>AIM is having some problems, sadly. I had the exact same issue.
You just have to wait until it finally blows over. It took mine about
an hour or so until it finally signed me in. I don&#039;t know how long it&#039;ll
be for you, but I wish you the best of luck.
Don&#039;t worry, you&#039;re not alone.
I thought someone hacked me too.
I&#039;m so relieved.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>O6gfbtJsaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>YoYoYiggityYo.</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267229137</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267301922</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>AIM is having some problems, sadly. I had the exact same issue.
You just have to wait until it finally blows over. It took mine about
an hour or so until it finally signed me in. I don&#039;t know how long it&#039;ll
be for you, but I wish you the best of luck.
Don&#039;t worry, you&#039;re not alone.
I thought someone hacked me too.
I&#039;m so relieved.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>4</Best>
            <UserId>O6gfbtJsaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>YoYoYiggityYo.</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-26 16:05:37</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267229137</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>omg i jus posted a question about this i thought someone hacked mine too, on my laptop it wouldnt let e see that captcha thing and it took like and hour for me to reset my password on my desktop and even tho i jus di that its still telling me i have the wrong username and password, but my old aol address is working jus fine.... hopefully we will be ok soon maybe its jus server problems??.....i hope</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>caHU7FqHaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Leann [[baby girl due 6/22/10]]</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-26 16:42:06</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267231326</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws03.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:48:44 PDT 2010 -->
