<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100303103851AA8D6YO" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Recent eBay purchase problem. How do I solve this. Any suggestions?</Subject>
    <Content>I recently sold a iPhone on eBay. The item sold to a buyer in Norway. 30 days have past and the buyer claims he has not received the iPhone. He instructed me on how to ship it. His paypal payment when received went under review and his address was unconfirmed. He did have a 100% feedback rating so I shipped the phone to his instructions. It ended up that he wanted it shipped a way there was no way of tracking it, which I did not know this at the time. I thought it could be tracked via customs number, which it can not. Upon review I found that his country Norway does not accept celluar devices into his country. What are my options. He says he is going to contact the authorities if I do not issue another phone of refund his money. Is this possible, do I have any defenses or do I have to refund his money. Is it possible to contact authorities on a matter like this. It has been a nightmare. I feel that if I refund the money I am admitting guilt, or I am being scammed.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-03 10:38:51</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267641531</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100303103851AA8D6YO</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>JyPRsHhBaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>WackaWacka1983</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I&#039;ve been on ebay 10+ yrs. Lack of tracking is one of the risks one assumes when buying/selling internationally. If you shipped it per his instructions, you bear no fault. Hopefully, you have some sort of proof of shipping which you can provide him.

I had a similar situation several yrs ago. I told the buyer there was no tracking &amp; once I shipped it, I assumed no responsibility. I don&#039;t know if I was being scammed or not. That&#039;s why I won&#039;t sell internationally any more I why I don&#039;t buy anything of real value internationally.

Don&#039;t issue a refund. It&#039;s not your fault. The buyer may automatically have some insurance from ebay or Paypal. If not, it&#039;s his loss.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>NssC624Zaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Tom</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267642906</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268160956</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I&#039;ve been on ebay 10+ yrs. Lack of tracking is one of the risks one assumes when buying/selling internationally. If you shipped it per his instructions, you bear no fault. Hopefully, you have some sort of proof of shipping which you can provide him.

I had a similar situation several yrs ago. I told the buyer there was no tracking &amp; once I shipped it, I assumed no responsibility. I don&#039;t know if I was being scammed or not. That&#039;s why I won&#039;t sell internationally any more I why I don&#039;t buy anything of real value internationally.

Don&#039;t issue a refund. It&#039;s not your fault. The buyer may automatically have some insurance from ebay or Paypal. If not, it&#039;s his loss.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>NssC624Zaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Tom</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-03 11:01:46</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267642906</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws14.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:18:07 PDT 2010 -->
