<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100318113957AAOq97c" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Do internet pirates profit from what they do?</Subject>
    <Content>I am writing a research paper on a possible ethical dilemma caused by internet piracy. (With main focus on the music industry and lately, the movie industry)

There has been one thing that I could not find though, and that is: those who upload material for others to download for free--do they profit in any way?  Do they distribute songs/movies/etc for free, and just do so because they feel like being nice to others? (besides the media industries, of course)

I know in a few cases, hackers would put viruses in pirated software in order to send it around. Or some sites may charge you; but please disregard those for now.  I am concerned with direct monetary gain or profit by the pirates themselves.

Any further comments regarding the morality of internet piracy is welcome as well!

Thanks in advance
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-18 11:39:57</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268937597</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100318113957AAOq97c</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>JL2p0iTyaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Kenworthe L</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Pirates enjoy what they do. And no, a good pirate group will not put any viruses in their uploaded files.

As far as I know, piracy has no profit for the pirates themselves. When it comes to videogames, they have to buy the game first and work on it to create a &quot;crack&quot;. Such groups of pirates crack games for a challenge, or sometimes to prove a point. Have you heard about the war between Ubisoft and pirates that&#039;s going on right now? Ubisoft released an offline game with a mechanic that makes it work like an online game, which makes it harder(maybe even impossible) to crack. Ubisoft&#039;s servers were attacked(probably by russian pirates) which makes the clients angry and demand the removal of such a mechanic, and some groups(in USA) are working on a crack to prove a point - every game can be cracked.

Pirates never talk about their activity publicly, so maybe they get a profit from something, but most likely not.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>8baUlWBoaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Norro</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269030971</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269457010</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>some people get payed to put adware in the software but for the most part people do it for fun or just for the challenge.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>O3mt4exBaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Kevin P</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-18 11:44:11</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268937851</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Most pirates just upload the files as a challenge. A lot of pirates will put viruses in the files to spread spam, steal credit card information, etc. Some well-known pirates will upload files for fame. Such as uploading new released movies a couple days after their premier.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>NNlTKNDcaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>codrr93</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-18 11:49:48</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268938188</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Pirates enjoy what they do. And no, a good pirate group will not put any viruses in their uploaded files.

As far as I know, piracy has no profit for the pirates themselves. When it comes to videogames, they have to buy the game first and work on it to create a &quot;crack&quot;. Such groups of pirates crack games for a challenge, or sometimes to prove a point. Have you heard about the war between Ubisoft and pirates that&#039;s going on right now? Ubisoft released an offline game with a mechanic that makes it work like an online game, which makes it harder(maybe even impossible) to crack. Ubisoft&#039;s servers were attacked(probably by russian pirates) which makes the clients angry and demand the removal of such a mechanic, and some groups(in USA) are working on a crack to prove a point - every game can be cracked.

Pirates never talk about their activity publicly, so maybe they get a profit from something, but most likely not.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>8baUlWBoaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Norro</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-19 13:36:11</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269030971</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws13.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:39:49 PDT 2010 -->
