<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100325130146AAbMzuc" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Where is the best place to register a domain name in the UK?</Subject>
    <Content>Online, what site should I use for a UK domain name registration? Thanks
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-25 13:01:46</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269547306</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100325130146AAbMzuc</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>1Pg7NZXnaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Badger Licker!!</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/49b9e1d6id61zul1re3/8qzTBJM8cqUyUInuQA.Sx6XkVXtgxrg.dQ--/1/tn48.jpg?ciAAToMB2IDutsYl</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>7</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Domain names are getting cheaper and cheaper because so many companies offer them. You do not say you want hosting or anything so i will list a few that i have used.

Heartinternet.co.uk
godaddy.com
just host.com

If you require hosting as well i recommend Godaddy.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>rugZxDXbaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Devastation Assistant</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269547697</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1270066526</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Domain names are getting cheaper and cheaper because so many companies offer them. You do not say you want hosting or anything so i will list a few that i have used.

Heartinternet.co.uk
godaddy.com
just host.com

If you require hosting as well i recommend Godaddy.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>rugZxDXbaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Devastation Assistant</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-25 13:08:17</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269547697</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Try http://www.inWebHosting.com , i have account with them and use it to Buy Domain Names, the WebHosting service is also cheap and reliable.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>bFN5m3Vmaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>GeekOnline</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-25 13:12:04</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269547924</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>You can register one here for £3 a year

http://www.internetbs.net/</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>SPzSkAz9aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Sanders</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-25 13:13:12</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269547992</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Cheapest place is not always best place to register domain.

It depends on what you are going to do with domain.

If you only want to sell it on then namecheap.com and godaddy.com are cheap and cheap or free to push to someone else&#039;s account.

If you are going to develop website on this domain, then you need to think about how and where you want your site hosted. If your site is intended primarily for UK then you want good UK based host, as slight boost in search engines is site is hosted in same country as market.

If your experienced with hosting problems and niggles, then you just want reliable, cheap UK host with minimum support.

If you are going to need help from time to time with things, then you need to make sure they provide adequate support, preferably telephone support.

I use 4uhosting.co.uk as I find them cheap and reliable but only offer minimum support,

I&#039;ve heard eukhost.com are ok and offer good support</Content>
            <Reference>many websites</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>zchczLEZaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Nosey One</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-25 13:48:05</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269550085</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>http://www.goldpuma.com is a cheap, reliable service to register UK domain names.

As you may know a domain name is just a name, not a real website. If you are going to create your website: 1- Buy a domain name. A domain name is a name you want to call your website (ex: www.yahoo.com). To get a domain name, you have to pay an annual fee to a registrar for the right to use that name. 2- Buy a web hosting service to provide your online space and enable you to get your website online at your purchased domain name.

If you want to start your website I recommend purchase your domain and hosting together. In this way it is possible to get your domain for free. Some hosting services offer this gift today.

As an experienced webmaster I recommend BH web hosting which I’m sure it would work for you and fulfill all your requirements. They have a really great offer for hosting &amp; I have used them for over 3 yrs now, and have never had a single problem with them. 

You can reach reviews about this web hosting provider and its latest DISCOUNT COUPONS at:


http://www.threehosts.com/reviews/1st

Only $3.95 /month (with discount coupon)


They also offer &quot;Free Site Builder&quot; that helps you build your web pages without difficulty if you are not skilled in using any website creating program (WYSIWYG: What You See Is What You Get). You can use this service optionally. You can also create the pages offline with your favorite program (DreamWeaver, FrontPage, Microsoft Publisher, iWeb etc.), and then upload them to your web host. This is another easy way to get your website online.

******IMPORTANT********
* This service was awarded the “Best Web Hosting OF The Year”.
* If you sign up for this service you will have $75 credits to advertise your website with the google &amp; yahoo search engines for free!
* You Can Register A Free Domain or Use Your Existing Domains. They Support All Domain Names.
****************************

Another useful link:
http://www.threehosts.com/build
There you can find a step-by-step guide to start your website.

Hope this helps.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>kNeMexGMaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>David M</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-25 15:52:29</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269557549</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I recommend either Namecheap or Godaddy.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>gtQQuylDaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Mark</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-27 17:00:55</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269734455</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Try iPage domain services which is a 10 year old company providing excellent and amazing service in Website Hosting and Domain Registration. The web hosting company offers Unlimited Disk Space and Unlimited Monthly Transfer on Bandwidth. iPage is offering great discount offer on its domain &amp; hosting services. http://www.webhostingbreak.com/ipage-domain-registration/</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>vMowEd4iaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Meg</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-29 05:04:34</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269864274</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws09.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:30:48 PDT 2010 -->
