<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100310212754AAio84t" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Formspring help despirate!!!?!?!?!!!! QUICK ANSWERS PLEASE!!!?</Subject>
    <Content>Ok so a few days ago i got a formspring. everything was fine. then 2 days ago i left facebook and formspring up and my siblings had written on some girls formspring that she saw on the facebook homepage. I didn&#039;t notice what she had done until today when they wrote on another girls account. then i saw what she had written on girl 1&#039;s account. Then i write on it apologizing that it was a mistake and the wrong account and try to cover it up by completely changing the image of the account. (on both) i feel terrible about what had happened in just a few days and by thinking about how schools is gonna be tomorrow. hell. so i just made up fake questions to cover up the mess. Then it gets worse. people knew it was me and they were writing me questions that were rude so i disabled my account. How can i deal with this in school tomorrow? What do i do? Its gonna be awful i can see it coming. 


What the sibs had written on the formsprings are 

Girl 2: are you prude? (they know more than you think)
Girl 1: do you like _______________? (because i had said to them that i don&#039;t think that girl likes me. 


I got myself into a huge mess trying to cover their act and i wasn&#039;t creeping at all. How can i deal with this?
0 seconds ago - 4 days left
what if ican&#039;t switch schools?  waht should i say to them?
Thanks edie!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-10 21:27:54</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268285274</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100310212754AAio84t</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>oMxdxqSbaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>MARIA</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>You shouldn&#039;t have covered it up in the first place. Just be honest and say, &quot;My sister was trying to play a prank. Sorry.&quot; Laugh it off too, and have your friends laugh it off with you. If they&#039;re still creeped out, just avoid appearing like a creeper for a while, even though you aren&#039;t anyway. But whatever you do, don&#039;t get super serious about it or get visibly upset if they don&#039;t believe you. That&#039;ll just make you look more suspicious.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>nBA89xE0aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Edie</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268285867</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268801011</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Go to a new school.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>F9m9qKBIaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Joseph</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-10 21:29:17</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268285357</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>You shouldn&#039;t have covered it up in the first place. Just be honest and say, &quot;My sister was trying to play a prank. Sorry.&quot; Laugh it off too, and have your friends laugh it off with you. If they&#039;re still creeped out, just avoid appearing like a creeper for a while, even though you aren&#039;t anyway. But whatever you do, don&#039;t get super serious about it or get visibly upset if they don&#039;t believe you. That&#039;ll just make you look more suspicious.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>nBA89xE0aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Edie</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-10 21:37:47</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268285867</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws02.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:15:10 PDT 2010 -->
