<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100225115833AAysUQj" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Does anyone know a website for teens and advice?</Subject>
    <Content>I&#039;m looking for a website where teens can talk, give/ask advice, and be in a stress relieving environment. I&#039;m about to be 16 years old soon. I need something for around my age.

Somewhere I can post a pick and ask advice about it or something like that. Talk about fashion, looks/appearances, and other day-to-day advice. A website that can help me turn my life around to be who I want to be, but it&#039;s very difficult for me.

Can anyone give me a list?
Thank you in advance.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-25 11:58:33</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267127913</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100225115833AAysUQj</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>seV1eR0Raa</UserId>
    <UserNick>(1&lt;3)</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://avatars.zenfs.com/users/14iZrIiOSAAEC9AFl3JbPFMoA.medium.png</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>4</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I&#039;m 16 and every now and then I go to www.girlslife.com :) Some users there are years younger than us, but some are about our age. So it&#039;s all good. Go check it out. :)</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>iomvyGYRaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Shoobibop</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267128031</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267375858</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I&#039;m 16 and every now and then I go to www.girlslife.com :) Some users there are years younger than us, but some are about our age. So it&#039;s all good. Go check it out. :)</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>iomvyGYRaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Shoobibop</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-25 12:00:31</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267128031</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>On the local radio station where I&#039;m from they talk about a website called boss of me or bom411.com i believe. I&#039;m not 100% sure if that&#039;s the actual site but if you google that it and it will bring you to the write one!</Content>
            <Reference>Local radio station 106.1 KMEL in the SF Bay Area</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>vMZgaFC3aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Emily</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-25 12:03:27</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267128207</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Your already on the site you want.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>X6WAOqZOaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Apotheosis001</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-25 12:04:29</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267128269</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I just took the word adolescence (I may have spelled it wrong) &amp; put it in the search above. Do that &amp; go to that area. I think normally you have to go through he pregnancy &amp; parenting to get to it...anyway, ask there cause I think a lot of teens are in that section &amp; you look at the Q &amp; A&#039;s that are there....there are always people who can be extremely rude or extremely nice &amp; helpful so take the good &amp; ignore the rest. I would also just do a search for yahoo groups &amp; you might find the specific groups you are looking for &amp; sometimes what you don&#039;t find on this site is here but you have to fine out where...for example I forget often that to ask a philosopy question I have to go through arts &amp; humanities so use the search to put words in for what you want &amp; just find your way around. I have answered many teen questions that have come from the psychology or mental health section so check them all out &amp; you might just want to build up a base of friends here...you would look for people you like &amp; then push the thing under their name that says something about them being a contact...you can build up a really nice bunch of friends her by doing that...you would go onto there questions often &amp; they might like you &amp; make you a contact &amp; help you a lot. If you have a specific problem though &amp; want a specific group just do a search outside of yahoo to find a group.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>I6dcRgD6aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Pra4USA</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-25 12:09:23</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267128563</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws06.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:56:57 PDT 2010 -->
