<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100225212024AAI8WVQ" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Please help me watch a show on-line!!?</Subject>
    <Content>I had to shut off cable because my husband would just watch the tv when he should have been watching our children, so since then I have been relying on the online shows to take abrief  break from everyday crap and lately it has been army wives and The bachelor that I have been wanting to watch, but they are not working anymore.  I can get them on my screen as before, but the keep needing to buffer I think.  The shows pause every 10 seconds or so to &quot;LOAD&quot; apparently whatever that means.  Anyway, now my huband is in Iraq, but I am keeping the cable off to save money, but I cant watch anything with my computer this way.  It use to work fine.  I set my control settings to med-high.  Itried deleting all the cookies, but it still did not due much.  Ihave a fairly new computer (bought it last year-gateway laptop) Please I just want a break to escape the kids, deployment, etc., can anyone help?  Oh and I have att internet service my speed is the lowest to buy but with my new computer should this be happening? Give me ideas!!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-25 21:20:24</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267161624</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100225212024AAI8WVQ</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>RyWNf9qEaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>busy bee</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL></UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>may be some conflicts with your flash player?
look for an alternative :)

10 Ways to Watch The Bachelor Online for Free!
http://techpp.com/2010/01/01/10-ways-to-watch-the-bachelor-season-14-episodes-online-for-free/</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>C5L4jbY7aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Kimly</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267453489</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267473941</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>may be some conflicts with your flash player?
look for an alternative :)

10 Ways to Watch The Bachelor Online for Free!
http://techpp.com/2010/01/01/10-ways-to-watch-the-bachelor-season-14-episodes-online-for-free/</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>4</Best>
            <UserId>C5L4jbY7aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Kimly</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 06:24:49</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267453489</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws12.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:53:19 PDT 2010 -->
