<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100302113321AAf8C1z" type="Answered">
    <Subject>sHOULD i REJOIN DEVINATART?</Subject>
    <Content>I was a member of deviant art foraboutt 8 months, and I got banned over a huge misunderstanding over art thieves and everything. I showed a lot of promise, and I loved that site.
I joined with a new account, but they banned me as I had the same email as my old account.
Idont know whether to join again. On one hand, I Love the site and really enjoy the people, my friends and the art there. BUt on the other hand, I got competitive with page views, but I am really worried they will ban me again.
Can the admins track your IP address down if you had another account? I know they can know your IP address, but can the da admins look up my old accounts ip and see if any new accounts have it? Or can they only see it if they specifically get drawn attention to me and cross reference my new account, and if see IM the same person?
Or would they need to know my old account, and someone tells them this is my new account, so they actually need to know both accounts, no just one. Im sorry, its all kinda confusing. Also, should I use the same characters I used to, or scrap all old ones and start over?
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-02 11:33:21</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267558401</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100302113321AAf8C1z</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>7pqqgA5Eaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Laura</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>1</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>What part of &#039;banned&#039; didn&#039;t you understand ??

OF COURSE the sysadmins keep a list of who&#039;s been banned (how else do they stop you joining again ?) .. and YES OF COURSE they have your IP Address ...

I&#039;ll give you just ONE hint ... PROXY SERVER ...

(hopefully if you are clever enough to work out how to get back on, you are clever enough not to get banned again ...)</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>86e0fcff22774bed26d5e5f6773ca754aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Steve B</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267568222</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268299353</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>What part of &#039;banned&#039; didn&#039;t you understand ??

OF COURSE the sysadmins keep a list of who&#039;s been banned (how else do they stop you joining again ?) .. and YES OF COURSE they have your IP Address ...

I&#039;ll give you just ONE hint ... PROXY SERVER ...

(hopefully if you are clever enough to work out how to get back on, you are clever enough not to get banned again ...)</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>86e0fcff22774bed26d5e5f6773ca754aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Steve B</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-02 14:17:02</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267568222</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws02.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:25:54 PDT 2010 -->
