<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100322172654AAlIyyI" type="Answered">
    <Subject>where online can I find a copy of my name change court paperwork?</Subject>
    <Content>ok i need that paperwork from 3 years ago. i want to save myself a stressful trip downtown. I can&#039;t find the final papers in my mess of an office. i filed in Sacramento, California.

the http://www.saccourt.ca.gov/ site says you can search for public records. i can&#039;t find my documents there. anyone have a clue where i can get a copy? i know it is a public document. there has to be a way to get it online. i will never change my name again, this has been the most frustrating experience. i just wanted to go back to my birth name. why didn&#039;t i put the correct name on my divorce paperwork. ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh. help!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-22 17:26:54</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269304014</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100322172654AAlIyyI</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>oh50yLCfaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Aubrey</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/4b61231fi4d3zul5sp1/zVft33gwbqTDKevV53R7EmRFrw--/2/tn48.jpg?ciAAToMB4vaz70_m</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Did you try
http://www.courtreference.com/California-Court-Search-Records.htm</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>T8E4D2T0aa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Kevin</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269304283</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269823609</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Did you try
http://www.courtreference.com/California-Court-Search-Records.htm</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>T8E4D2T0aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Kevin</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-22 17:31:23</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269304283</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I am sad you felt the need to change your name, but this will never change the person for if I was close I would come to the office and help. Relax your mind and enjoy the Gift of life.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>Bz2OtXMWaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>STEFAN N</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-23 02:13:22</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269335602</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Hi,

If you have lost the document showing your name change or want to revert back to your birth name you can do this through a Deed Poll document. It is a relatively cheap process and will show your name change from your current name back to your former name or another name of your choice.

You can apply for a Deed Poll document online for as little as £29. If you cannot find your just order another one. Probably be a lot less stressful than hunting all over the place for yours!

Check out this site for more info:

http://www.ukdp.co.uk/apply-now/how-it-works/

It can all be done over the internet as well which will be easier probably-hope this helps

Good Luck</Content>
            <Reference>www.ukdp.co.uk</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>ugPoRrUVaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Tabby</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-23 09:20:59</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269361259</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws04.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:21:10 PDT 2010 -->
