<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100306115820AAXPQYn" type="Answered">
    <Subject>Two quick questions about buying on Ebay?</Subject>
    <Content>1. Can a seller on ebay accept a payment from a credit card, or do all payments on Ebay now have to go through PayPal? I&#039;m trying to find out if you can use a credit card to make a payment without having a PayPal account. I realize that when you pay a seller you are sending the payment to the seller&#039;s PayPal address.

2. If you purchased an item using a credit card (not PayPal) wouldn&#039;t it show up as a purchase at your &quot;My Ebay&quot; page? Or, is it that only items that are paid through PayPal appear as item recently bought?
I am trying to find out if when you make a payment using a CREDIT CARD (not paying with PayPal)-- a &quot;but it now&quot; offer from an Ebay store-- wouldn&#039;t the item still appear as an item that you recently bought (the buying activity) on your &quot;My Ebay&quot; homepage.
Miagi99: I can&#039;t decipher your answer!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-06 11:58:20</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267905500</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100306115820AAXPQYn</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>AA11424947</UserId>
    <UserNick>What I Say</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://a323.yahoofs.com/coreid/49cbd73di24d7zul1sp1/dXXWrXQhfrK4LmIraE404QU-/1/tn48.png?ciAAToMBOCh8haEd</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>2</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>No, only items bought through paypal automatically appear as payed until the seller authorizes the payment and marks it as payed is when ebay recognizes it as being payed.  Some sellers have their own payment methods seperate from ebay and you can still pay through credit card most of these are actual ebay stores.  To setup payment other than paypal just ask the seller.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>QxERY26Laa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Miagi99</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267905916</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268439145</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>No, only items bought through paypal automatically appear as payed until the seller authorizes the payment and marks it as payed is when ebay recognizes it as being payed.  Some sellers have their own payment methods seperate from ebay and you can still pay through credit card most of these are actual ebay stores.  To setup payment other than paypal just ask the seller.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>QxERY26Laa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Miagi99</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 12:05:16</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267905916</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>A seller can accept payment by Credit card if they are set up for that.  Some of the eBay store offer that option but most common folk do NOT.

Don&#039;t quite understand the second question  but suffice to say anything you purchased via eBay will show up on your eBay page, whether you use Paypal, credit card, cash or money order.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>HWoEiKPMaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Sattamander</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-06 12:28:08</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267907288</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws15.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:47:34 PDT 2010 -->
