<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100322211020AAAzYPH" type="Answered">
    <Subject>any real moms know how to make money from home?</Subject>
    <Content>i have a new baby and cant work outside of home is there any legit online jobs that pay real money??
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-22 21:10:20</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269317420</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100322211020AAAzYPH</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>Z2tTyvzNaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Mikky</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>8</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I have something interesting for you, RupeeMail!

It’s really amazing! You get paid to open &amp; read the contents of
RupeeMail. You receive promotional offers &amp; special discounts in
RupeeMail.

Interestingly RupeeMails will reach you based on the preference list
you opted for.

Create your RupeeMail Account &amp; refer your friends to earn launch
referral bonus on every new registration.

Try this... http://www.rupeemail.in/rupeemail/invite.do?in=NTU0NTM5JSMlcXprUWpnMTJFdHZuZEZhZVBPbExXQnc0VQ==

RupeeMail, It pay</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>9SNKaJUeaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>sahib s</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269337196</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1269836759</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>not a mom lol, but i have tried the online route, there&#039;s data entry jobs that can pay up to $75 an hour but usually u have to be employed by a company to get those kinds of rates, the sign up ones will give u no more than $15 an hour. Same applies with survey&#039;s if ur employed by an actual company rather than signing ur self up ull get much more cash.
Also the one&#039;s that u sign up 4, they usually have a cumulative effect, meaning that even though u earn a few dollars for every survey or whatever u can&#039;t withdraw the money until u&#039;ve reached a minimum amount of say $100 which is fine unless u need the money straight away.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>z7GIIesAaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>VE9A</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-22 21:22:01</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269318121</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Work from Home. Earn Rs.2,000 daily. No Investment. Part Time Jobs.

Wanted Online Internet job workers. Job is only through Internet. Work from home part time jobs. You can earn Rs.750-2000/- daily. These are genuine Data entry jobs &amp; Internet jobs. No Investment required. Only serious enquires please. For more details visit http://www.earnparttimejobs.com/index.php?id=2717314</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>UyZCOFb4aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>kumar</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-22 21:56:33</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269320193</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I have something interesting for you, RupeeMail!

It’s really amazing! You get paid to open &amp; read the contents of
RupeeMail. You receive promotional offers &amp; special discounts in
RupeeMail.

Interestingly RupeeMails will reach you based on the preference list
you opted for.

Create your RupeeMail Account &amp; refer your friends to earn launch
referral bonus on every new registration.

Try this... http://www.rupeemail.in/rupeemail/invite.do?in=NTU0NTM5JSMlcXprUWpnMTJFdHZuZEZhZVBPbExXQnc0VQ==

RupeeMail, It pay</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>9SNKaJUeaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>sahib s</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-23 02:39:56</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269337196</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Auto content cash is simply a remote control to generate fine quality automatic content for your passive income earning WordPress sites. Auto content cash is a tutorial course that provides strategies, methods, blue prints and systems to assist internet marketers to create an automated content which would enhance their profits. 

The auto content cash provides simple solution to the problem of continuous upgrading of websites and blogs.

It assures them to access tricks and strategies in generating quality content in just few seconds. Whosoever is serious about earning an online living should not miss an opportunity to avail this bonus as it would help them to earn thousands of dollars.

http://www.cprof.org</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.cprof.org/business-internet/auto-content-cash-review-overview.html</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>bbKmR1n8aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Jiow</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-23 09:01:13</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269360073</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>It all depends on what skills you have. What you need is a variety of things to try out, and find what fits for YOU.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>1eItvbl0aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Ross</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-23 09:35:15</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269362115</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Hi there,
Most people expect to start making money online fast by doing next to nothing and these are the people that mostly fall for the scams because they are expecting to make big money by doing nothing and I&#039;m sorry to tell you but you can&#039;t!! Don&#039;t get me wrong people do make money online and there are ways to make big amounts of money online but it takes time and effort and usually an investment. I recently joined a company that allows you to work from home and in 1 month I have managed to make a residual income of $350 and that is growing. It&#039;s not loads but its a great start! I’m really excited about this company and I really hope you can see the potential and join my team. Proof of my income and more info is available at my site......
http://www.infinitydownline2up.com/html/paul.html
Trust me when I tell you this.....You are not going to find a better opportunity and you are not going to find something where you can earn money fast and easy I know because I have tried everything from paid surveys to mailing envelopes from home which all turned out to be a waste of time and money! I provide full training on how to really make money online and I manage to do it so there is absolutely no reason why you can&#039;t!!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>xpZaR2WOaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Paul</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-23 16:46:58</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269388018</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Don&#039;t trust the spammers of Yahoo Answers who&#039;s account has been created recently. I take surveys every single day and I am a credible source (check how long I&#039;ve been on Yahoo answers for). Opinionoutpost pays about $8.00 an hour which isn&#039;t bad considering you get to listen to music when you are taking surveys. They send you about 3 surveys a day (10-20 minutes each). This is the highest paid survey site I am currently on. Feel free to email me with any questions about this site and fill out the short charts about yourself so they can send more paid surveys to you.

http://OpinionOutpost.com/join/7275641</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>g0WLiXa1aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>I&#039;m a man</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-23 19:48:31</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269398911</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Earn money online FREE!!

Any one From Any part of the world can start earning!!

Its 100% Genuine.

I have my own payment proof available.

http://bit.ly/BAisy

If u further need any help regarding it mail me at : nadeem_2008in@yahoo.co.in</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>hNZIkiQJaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>nadz</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-25 00:07:14</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269500834</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws13.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 20:20:29 PDT 2010 -->
