<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100326132556AAD35we" type="Answered">
    <Subject>How do you get more followers on twitter?</Subject>
    <Content>How do you get more followers on twitter? My Twitter: JERICHOFAN4LIFE
http://twitter.com/JERICHOFAN4LIFE
I have a youtube 
http://www.youtube.com/user/1JERICHOFAN4LIFE
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-26 13:25:56</Date>
    <Timestamp>1269635156</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100326132556AAD35we</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>jI7dSmMBaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Chantelle</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>5</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I followed you.  @targetfollow

I find Twitter trains a great way to get followers.  First, you sign into the website, follow people, then you get added to the train.  Once you&#039;re on the train, people that sign up then have to follow you.  It&#039;s all people looking to get more followers, so it works well.  Give this one a try:  http://targetfollowers.com</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>OJyts4ptaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>stevendbrady</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1269834757</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1270154741</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>You gotta be something interesting, if you aren&#039;t, then what&#039;s the point?
You can&#039;t just arbitrarily make people join you.  Get recognized on youtube or facebook, then when you do, you got followers who have no life of their own, like me :D</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>4M9r1wNoaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>jrd_t</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-26 13:28:56</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269635336</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Interacting with people lets others know you are neither spam nor a bot. Also try searching people that have the same interests that you do, follow and connect with them.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>9PFh4BcSaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Kim Randall</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-26 13:29:35</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269635375</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>TweetMiner has a friend suggestion feature that you might find useful. You can enter search keywords and it will work 24/7 looking for people who match the search keywords you enter.

So let&#039;s say you were interested in cars you could enter search keywords like #autos, #cars, #vans, #mechanic

It&#039;s good to use #tags because then you can be sure you&#039;re finding people who went to the trouble of writing a #hashtag in their tweet.

When TM makes the suggestions you can simply click a &quot;follow&quot; button. hopefully they will follow you back and now you&#039;ve found a follower who you share stuff in common with.

Check out the short &quot;Grow Your Following&quot; section on this page.... http://tweetminer.net/demo

TweetMiner is Free (but does have some subscription plans for power users)

You can also do the same thing on twitter (but it&#039;s more of a manual process) by going to search.twitter.com and entering in your #tags there and seeing if anyone interesting comes back in the search results. However I will say TweetMiner makes the process easier!

Hope this helps!</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>btgJHao6aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Justin V</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-26 16:40:46</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269646846</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>You get followers on Twitter by following others. However, you want to follow people who are interested in the things that you are interested in. Therefore, you want to make a list of things that you are interested in or a list of things that you will be primarily discussing via your Twitter page and then find people who are tweeting about those things.

Once you have your list, sign-up for this free Twitter application (see link below) that will allow you to set-up your list of keywords and follow up to 30 people who are tweeting about them. There is a strong possibility that these people will follow you back because of a shared interest.

Here&#039;s the link to sign up for the free application: 

http://tweetspinner.com/7091707

Join my Facebook Fan page called Web Marketers Speak or send an @reply via Twitter to 
http://www.twitter.com/webmktrsspk if you need further assistance.</Content>
            <Reference>Web Marketers Speak: http://www.webmarketersspeak.info</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>zo6sV08Vaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Webmktrsspk</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-28 12:23:58</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269804238</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I followed you.  @targetfollow

I find Twitter trains a great way to get followers.  First, you sign into the website, follow people, then you get added to the train.  Once you&#039;re on the train, people that sign up then have to follow you.  It&#039;s all people looking to get more followers, so it works well.  Give this one a try:  http://targetfollowers.com</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>OJyts4ptaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>stevendbrady</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-28 20:52:37</Date>
            <Timestamp>1269834757</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws02.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:26:20 PDT 2010 -->
