<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100228191434AAVOKYz" type="Answered">
    <Subject>What web host do you use and why?</Subject>
    <Content>I want to have my own site, but I&#039;d like it to have my name, not something.something-else.com
How much does it cost you, is the service, if any, good? How much space do you get/use, and so on.

:] Thank-you in advance!
</Content>
    <Date>2010-02-28 19:14:34</Date>
    <Timestamp>1267413274</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100228191434AAVOKYz</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>HIHz4jh9aa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Lovette</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>16</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>I recommend one of these: http://www.tophostingpicks.com

iPage has the best offer right now.
Their standard price is $84/year ($6.95) but they have
a 50% sale, one year of hosting for $42.00.

Their plan includes:

Unlimited disk space
Unlimited bandwidth
Free domain name

Price: $42/year ($3.50)

They have one of the most popular hosting platforms, which currently hosts over a million websites. They&#039;re also one of the oldest hosting companies, founded in 1998.

They include a free point &amp; click online site builder so you can create a website without any programming (easily, just by drag and drop) or you could install Wordpress (they include easy, one click install from their control panel), choose a theme that you like, and start adding content.

They also have a great custom control panel with OneClick installs of all the popular software like Wordpress, Joomla, Forums, Chat, Galleries, Online stores and a lot more.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>wxk9vTfCaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>John</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1267489710</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1267932907</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I use Microsoft Office Live.  It&#039;s pretty easy to use as far as creating a webpage goes and they provide many in-depth graphs on site traffic and where the viewers are coming from.

When I signed up with the program I got a one year free .com domain name which is now I believe $14/year.

Not trying to spam, but if you want to check out a sample of a website made with Office Live, my site is:

www.businessjingles.com

I would recommend Office Live.  It has many more details and features which you can learn from their website.  Good luck!</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.officelive.com/en-us/</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>6RDFADIYaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>David</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-28 19:21:22</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267413682</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>nearlyfreespeech.net

It is pay as you use.  I love the idea.

I spent $50+ a year with GoDaddy.  I have not even spent $20 yet and I have been with them for 6 months.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>e15cfb38ea606847ece9c1f6ee134021aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>mashyoucameron</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-28 19:22:41</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267413761</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>About $110 will buy you a robust hosting for 12 months with excellent 24 hour tech support within US.

It&#039;s unlimited space, with your own e-mail, auto responder, web templates, you can create your own forum, your own Webpress blog FREE domain registration as long as your hosting it with this company.

I&#039;ve used different sites in the past and for the past 8 years this Hosting stands to be the best.

Word of caution if you are planning on registering your Domain name stay as far away from Go Daddy as possible...they are the worst to deal with.

PM me if you need help in setting up. 

Good Luck,

Jesse</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>7be87530199492a0eb6cc057f967dd3eaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Jesse  a.k. a Leojin</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-28 19:25:47</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267413947</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I use http://ultrawebsitehosting.com for my sites and they have been really great.

I also use http://dynadot.com to register my domain names. 

Also see http://choosingyourwebhost.com to make a decision on what type of hosting is right for your site.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>zopRHh9taa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Chad</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-28 19:54:46</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267415686</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>hostmonster
$5/month including domain name
tons of modules
unlimited traffic, space, (just about everything)
excellent service
hosted in the us
excellent uptime
supports php, mysql
multiple domains (sites) on one account
lots more...
I can&#039;t say enough good about them - I&#039;ve been using them for several years now without a single problem.</Content>
            <Reference>www.hostmonster.com</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>fd9rbJYhaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Mel</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-02-28 20:22:42</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267417362</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I run a few small sites on the internet, and free hosting fulfills everything I need, I recently found http://hypersink.com, it is totally free and as good as a paid hosting plan, cant beat it! The best one I have found in all the years I have played on the internet.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>esbTHaDUaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Adrian</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 01:27:31</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267435651</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>As an experienced webmaster I recommend BH web hosting which I’m sure it would work for you and fulfill all your requirements. They have a really great offer for hosting &amp; I have used them for over 3 yrs now, and have never had a single problem with them.

You can reach reviews about this web hosting provider and its latest DISCOUNT COUPONS at:

http://www.threehosts.com/reviews/1st

Only $3.95 /month (with discount coupon).

******IMPORTANT********
* This service was awarded the “Best Web Hosting OF The Year”.
* If you sign up for this service you will have $75 credits to advertise your website with the google &amp; yahoo search engines for free!
* You Can Register A Free Domain or Use Your Existing Domains. They Support All Domain Names.
****************************

Another useful link:
http://www.threehosts.com/build
There you can find a step-by-step guide to start your website.

Hope this helps.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>03BYdQiAaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>David M</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 06:48:06</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267454886</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>iPage is one of the finest website hosting available over the internet. There are many but to choose the best is not easy. Just checked with Webhostingbreak and found their services very reliable. For the past many months, I&#039;m using their services. Very much amazing, how quickly they resolve any issues. The web hosting servers are very fast. &gt;&gt; http://p.gs/08i5e</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>Y01vFxTFaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Allan</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 07:44:33</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267458273</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Hi,

I mostly use Justhost, Powweb and others. I recommend Justhost for a number of reasons. They give you the most, they back up their service with a anytime money back guarantee. You can change your mind two months down the road and they will refund the rest of your money. Unlimited space, emails, free domain for life.

I help people start their own websites, and I dont charge to help. You can contact me .</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>N0zZc7avaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>John S</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 12:45:52</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267476352</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Just Host. $2.95/month with coupon &quot;50 OFF&quot;. Here you go http://www.flavr.be/justhost
2 years experience, no problems, great and FAST support, really cheap and so on. You have to check it out.</Content>
            <Reference>http://www.flavr.be/justhost</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>txJd7J3Iaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Asdasd</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 13:32:53</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267479173</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I recommend one of these: http://www.tophostingpicks.com

iPage has the best offer right now.
Their standard price is $84/year ($6.95) but they have
a 50% sale, one year of hosting for $42.00.

Their plan includes:

Unlimited disk space
Unlimited bandwidth
Free domain name

Price: $42/year ($3.50)

They have one of the most popular hosting platforms, which currently hosts over a million websites. They&#039;re also one of the oldest hosting companies, founded in 1998.

They include a free point &amp; click online site builder so you can create a website without any programming (easily, just by drag and drop) or you could install Wordpress (they include easy, one click install from their control panel), choose a theme that you like, and start adding content.

They also have a great custom control panel with OneClick installs of all the popular software like Wordpress, Joomla, Forums, Chat, Galleries, Online stores and a lot more.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>wxk9vTfCaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>John</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-01 16:28:30</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267489710</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Making a website isn&#039;t as easy as first thought. It can be done within 2 minutes but for new people to hosting it may take longer.

For the domain (what the website is called), I would use http://www.co.cc (FREE). However is will be something.co.cc . You can get others such as .com and .co.uk but they are not free. The cheapest place for these type is http://123-reg.com.

Then for the Host, I would use http://www.000webhost.com/247474.html (FREE)

The host is the place that your site is located, and the domain is where it is shown on the web.
http://www.000webhost.com/247474.html has 1500MB of space and 100GB of bandwidth (Both are more than enough you will need).

I use 000webhost even for my paid domains, as it is really good and has loads of features from the starters to advances such as wp-install mySQL etc.</Content>
            <Reference>MY sites</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>4LIbHFPpaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Ell D</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-02 11:18:28</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267557508</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>I use FatCow. With FatCow you simply need to manage the control panel which is easy to use. The control panel is the best in the industry, Vdeck. If you want to learn more about how the control panel works, you simply can refer to the help pages.

The FatCow also provides stylish and professional ready to use web templates. You just need to customize the web template to suit your taste and needs. There are hundreds of designs to choose from. &gt;&gt; http://p.gs/eysde</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>rzoPqRP9aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Bob</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-03 06:49:49</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267627789</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>i like fatcow because it&#039;s very good hosting.  i personally use it for my blog site.  it&#039;s also cheap.
they have sitebuilder where you can build your own site without programming experience. unlimited space and bandwidth. free domain.  check out
Compare Top Web Hosts: http://www.compare-top-web-hosts.com/</Content>
            <Reference>Compare Top Web Hosts: http://www.compare-top-web-hosts.com/</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>zlrn7S2Caa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Yoman</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-03 08:46:04</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267634764</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>http://WebStarts.com?aff=sumar

easy, fast and cheap!

enjoy</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>Y1OpB7Lxaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>sumar</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-03 09:53:32</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267638812</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>well in my opinion u can think about www.myhostingweb.com  . i have my website with them, this is cool company, they have feature that when u will sign up, u will have to pay just for domain name,about 10$ per year, and then for web space u will have option to pay after two months, so if u like their hosting facilities then u can host with them, otherwise u can transfer ur domain to another host, and if u paywhile shin up, then u will have 30 days money back guarantee , so depend on u, either u wanna pay after two months or at the same time of sign up, their plans starts from INR - 40 per month = US $ 0.8 per month to 5 or 6 $ per month, its ur choice whichever u like to go with, well u will get all the facilities like fantastico, site builder, whm , cpanel, site configuration software, rv skin. and many more things, i have been with them for last twomonths and till now no any problem, they said they have their server in usa, and when i tried to whois search then i found them right, they r having theplanet.com  dedicated servers,at the same place where  hostgator   has their servers, so its cool company, try it, they r new in this market so may be bcoz of it, they r having attacking marketing policy, but they r cool.</Content>
            <Reference>http://myhostingweb.com</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>SkIVYykpaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>pokahai18</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-03 10:41:13</Date>
            <Timestamp>1267641673</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws15.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Wed Apr  7 01:35:07 PDT 2010 -->
