<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100308200449AAvp0Cv" type="Answered">
    <Subject>I NEED 2 NO HOW 2 GET MY PERENTS 2 NOT NOTICE ME LOOK AT PORN!!!?</Subject>
    <Content>i am looking 4 a way 2 look at porn wothout my parent knowing coz they are checking my internet junk. i just dont know how they find out!!! they dont have any perental controll on this pc, but i do know that my dad was looking through my temporary internet files. soo plzz tell me any possible way they could fint out what ive been browsing on.
</Content>
    <Date>2010-03-08 20:04:49</Date>
    <Timestamp>1268107489</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100308200449AAvp0Cv</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>gldCZCuBaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Pie189</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>4</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>1</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>First of all, delete all of ure history, including cache cookies passwords, EVERYTHING, secondly, use a proxy server, like hidemyass.com. Also, if u want to go extreme, you could install a different browser everyday, then uninstall after ure done. But ya ure dad probably sees ure history of ure cookies.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>lguR0SfSaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>Ace</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1268108143</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1268159803</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Eyyyy, lol go to hidemyass.com and then wen u get to that site, then on the site type the site u want, and lol you sound too young for porn</Content>
            <Reference>google.com</Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>s4mUMRpgaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Who knows</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 20:12:35</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268107955</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>you can delete the history and temporary files. this should help... make sure you have pop up blockers so no porn pops pop up while ur parents are on the pc</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>7xmNe7QWaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>bree20</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 20:13:43</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268108023</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>First of all, delete all of ure history, including cache cookies passwords, EVERYTHING, secondly, use a proxy server, like hidemyass.com. Also, if u want to go extreme, you could install a different browser everyday, then uninstall after ure done. But ya ure dad probably sees ure history of ure cookies.</Content>
            <Reference>My head, proxy server: hidemyass.com, but there are a billion others</Reference>
            <Best>4</Best>
            <UserId>lguR0SfSaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Ace</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-08 20:15:43</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268108143</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>You Don&#039;t.

Please Realize that Porn Destroys, See How it has destroyed the Lives of those who were involved in the Industry as seen in this Video

Dead Porn Stars Memorial www.shelleylubben.com
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r0q_VGacfNk

By far, the most searched for terms on the internet are related to pornography. Pornography is rampant in the world today. Perhaps more than anything else, Satan has succeeded in twisting and perverting sex. He has taken what is good and right (loving sex between a husband and wife) and replaced it with lust, pornography, adultery, rape, and homosexuality. Pornography can be the first step on a very slippery slope of ever-increasing wickedness and immorality (Romans 6:19). The addictive nature of pornography is well documented. Just as a drug user must consume greater and more powerful quantities of drugs to achieve the same “high,” pornography drags a person deeper and deeper into hard-core sexual addictions and ungodly desires. 

The three main categories of sin are the lust of the flesh, the lust of the eyes, and the pride of life (1 John 2:16). Pornography definitely causes us to lust after flesh, and it is undeniably a lust of the eyes. Pornography definitely does not qualify as one of the things we are to think about, according to Philippians 4:8. Pornography is addictive (1 Corinthians 6:12; 2 Peter 2:19), and destructive (Proverbs 6:25-28; Ezekiel 20:30; Ephesians 4:19). Lusting after other people in our minds, which is the essence of pornography, is offensive to God (Matthew 5:28). When habitual devotion to pornography characterizes a person’s life, it demonstrates the person is not saved (1 Corinthians 6:9).

For those involved in pornography, God can and will give the victory. Are you involved with pornography and desire freedom from it? Here are some steps to victory: 1) Confess your sin to God (1 John 1:9). 2) Ask God to cleanse, renew, and transform your mind (Romans 12:2). 3) Ask God to fill your mind with Philippians 4:8. 4) Learn to possess your body in holiness (1 Thessalonians 4:3-4). 5) Understand the proper meaning of sex and rely on your spouse alone to meet that need (1 Corinthians 7:1-5). 6) Realize that if you walk in the Spirit, you will not fulfill the lusts of the flesh (Galatians 5:16). 7) Take practical steps to reduce your exposure to graphic images. Install pornography blockers on your computer, limit television and video usage, and find another Christian who will pray for you and help keep you accountable.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>XN0cYCATaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Lightning From the East</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-09 06:28:57</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268144937</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
        <Comment>
            <Content></Content>
            <UserId>T8gEmCtEaa</UserId>
            <UserNick></UserNick>
            <Date>2010-03-09 15:22:33</Date>
            <Timestamp>1268144937</Timestamp>
        </Comment>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws03.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 21:28:16 PDT 2010 -->
