<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<ResultSet xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="urn:yahoo:answers" xsi:schemaLocation="urn:yahoo:answers http://answers.yahooapis.com/AnswersService/V1/AnswerResponse.xsd">
  <Question id="20100401065230AARnXNh" type="Answered">
    <Subject>help me please!!!!!!!!!!?</Subject>
    <Content>A girl on webs keeps bullying me. i said to her I love you as a friend, you know like what girls do. (this was before anything happened) then she gets mad that I talk to her lot and pretty much said i talk to you a lot because you are so much fun to talk to. I don&#039;t talk to her 24/7. the next day she gets mad and everything goes wrong. some of this is my fault cuz I asked her i know you are mad. and stuff. and so we get in a fight. Then I ask her to forgive me. She keeps ignoring. and I told her can&#039;t we just forgive and forget! she says. What the heck? Yu are such a creeper and a stalker ( she said the stalker part at another time but yeah:() and if you say anything else I will call the police. i am scared and I started crying! I do not know what I did!! I know this is part of my fault because I asked her but I am really scared! HELP!!

PS no mean comments or comments with bad words

PSS i need help not more hurt
</Content>
    <Date>2010-04-01 06:52:31</Date>
    <Timestamp>1270129951</Timestamp>
    <Link>http://answers.yahoo.com/question/?qid=20100401065230AARnXNh</Link>
    <Category id="2115500139">Other - Internet</Category>
    <UserId>pgtdXxPFaa</UserId>
    <UserNick>Amber</UserNick>
    <UserPhotoURL>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/identity/nopic_48.gif</UserPhotoURL>
    <NumAnswers>3</NumAnswers>
    <NumComments>0</NumComments>
    <ChosenAnswer>Best thing to do in this case, regardless of how difficult it will be, is to wait it out. She wants you to back off, so back off and wait for her to come back to you. Be prepared to lose contact with her, however. Don&#039;t push the issue, you&#039;ll only make things worse. Be patient. Easier said than done - I know.</ChosenAnswer>
    <ChosenAnswererId>OlMQHOzSaa</ChosenAnswererId>
    <ChosenAnswererNick>techmonkey</ChosenAnswererNick>
    <ChosenAnswerTimestamp>1270130311</ChosenAnswerTimestamp>
    <ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>1270254538</ChosenAnswerAwardTimestamp>
    <Answers>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Don&#039;t worry about the police thing, you haven&#039;t done any criminal act so they can&#039;t charge you. Maybe you should just...forget about her? It&#039;s only someone you know online right, you dont know her for real? So im sure you can get over her.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>uTLHft08aa</UserId>
            <UserNick>Mike C</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-04-01 06:56:21</Date>
            <Timestamp>1270130181</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Best thing to do in this case, regardless of how difficult it will be, is to wait it out. She wants you to back off, so back off and wait for her to come back to you. Be prepared to lose contact with her, however. Don&#039;t push the issue, you&#039;ll only make things worse. Be patient. Easier said than done - I know.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best>5</Best>
            <UserId>OlMQHOzSaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>techmonkey</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-04-01 06:58:31</Date>
            <Timestamp>1270130311</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
        <Answer>
            <Content>Dont contact her anymore or you&#039;re gonna get yourself in some hot water. Walk away from it and dont provoke her to call the police. That will only get you in more trouble.....just let it go and leave her be.</Content>
            <Reference></Reference>
            <Best></Best>
            <UserId>S16zm2jAaa</UserId>
            <UserNick>jon</UserNick>
            <Date>2010-04-01 07:01:16</Date>
            <Timestamp>1270130476</Timestamp>
        </Answer>
    </Answers>
    <Comments>
    </Comments>
  </Question>
</ResultSet>
<!-- ws10.ydn.gq1.yahoo.com uncompressed/chunked Tue Apr  6 19:11:42 PDT 2010 -->
